<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>Media Tips</title>
  
  <subtitle>Enjoy life easier but more creative!</subtitle>
  <link href="https://media-tips.techidaily.com/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  
  <link href="https://media-tips.techidaily.com/"/>
  <updated>2024-08-29T04:44:58.000Z</updated>
  <id>https://media-tips.techidaily.com/</id>
  
  <author>
    <name>Kenneth</name>
    
  </author>
  
  <generator uri="https://hexo.io/">Hexo</generator>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Expanding Viewership: Tablo Introduces Enhanced OTA DVR with Impressive 8TB Capacity</title>
    <link href="https://media-tips.techidaily.com/expanding-viewership-tablo-introduces-enhanced-ota-dvr-with-impressive-8tb-capacity/"/>
    <id>https://media-tips.techidaily.com/expanding-viewership-tablo-introduces-enhanced-ota-dvr-with-impressive-8tb-capacity/</id>
    <published>2024-08-28T15:59:40.000Z</published>
    <updated>2024-08-29T04:44:58.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="Expanding-Viewership-Tablo-Introduces-Enhanced-OTA-DVR-with-Impressive-8TB-Capacity"><a href="#Expanding-Viewership-Tablo-Introduces-Enhanced-OTA-DVR-with-Impressive-8TB-Capacity" class="headerlink" title="Expanding Viewership: Tablo Introduces Enhanced OTA DVR with Impressive 8TB Capacity"></a>Expanding Viewership: Tablo Introduces Enhanced OTA DVR with Impressive 8TB Capacity</h2><p>Some of you cord-cutters out there might be familiar with the name Tablo. If you cancelled your cable or satellite TV provider, or never had it in the first place, a Tablo DVR will let you access some <a class="link"   href="https://sound-issues.techidaily.com/how-to-fix-a-non-functioning-steelseries-arctis-pro-microphone-complete-solution/" >free local OTA channels <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> in addition to the streaming services you’re currently subscribed to. Now, Tablo has released a fourth-gen DVR, and it’s better than ever.</p><p> Tablo has introduced a sleek new DVR model. The most notable feature, apart from the new stylish white round design, is the fact that it comes with up to 128GB of storage as well as the option to add up to 8TB via external hard drives, possibly making it the ultimate recording DVR. It also integrates live free streaming channels into Tablo’s live TV guide, similar to Roku TVs, and it has also launched a new app compatible with various platforms such as Roku, Amazon Fire TV, Android TV&#x2F;Google TV, iOS mobile, and smart TVs. Apple TV, Samsung, and Vizio are also expected to join the list later in the year. It’s worth noting that the apps are required to use the device — there’s no HDMI output on the DVR itself.</p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static1.howtogeekimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/tabloonly_product_images_r2-1.jpg"                      alt="TabloOnly_Product_Images_R2-1"                > </p><p>Tablo</p><p> The DVR supports wireless streaming of live and recorded TV to any screen within the home, including smart TVs, streaming devices, smartphones, and tablets via Wi-Fi or Ethernet. Tablo’s mobile app will also help you set up both the antenna and Tablo device, optimizing reception and channel availability based on the home’s proximity to broadcast towers.</p><p> Nuvyyo CEO Grant Hall said in the announcement, “consumers struggling with inflation are looking for more affordable ways to enjoy live sports, local news and must-watch TV events.” He also went on to add that “with a live TV guide that spans the best in live broadcast TV and free live streaming content, one-touch series recording as well as customized content recommendations, Tablo has evolved beyond a way to enhance your antenna TV experience to an affordable portal to free TV without a subscription.”</p><p> Sadly, there’s no support for ATSC 3.0 (also known as “NextGen TV”), which would allow 4K channels and other features. DVR and tuner manufacturers are <a class="link"   href="https://techidaily.com/solutions-to-restore-deleted-files-from-tecno-by-fonelab-android-recover-data/" >still working on support <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> for the DRM now in use on some ATSC 3.0 stations, and it seems like Tablo didn’t want to put the launch on hold just for that. The FAQ on the product page explains, “The tuners in the 4th generation Tablo support the ATSC 1.0 broadcast standard used by all major commercial broadcasts today and the Tablo device takes full advantage of it like never before. While ATSC 3.0 broadcasts are available in some markets, ATSC 1.0 broadcasts will continue through at least June 2027.”</p><p> If this sounds like a cool addition to your home, <a class="link"   href="https://www.tablotv.com/product/?v=tablo" >this new Tablo DVR <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> can be had for an MSRP of $129.95 with an antenna and $99.95 without one, although as of the time of writing, you can grab the antenna-equipped one for $109.95.</p><p> Source: <a class="link"   href="https://cordcuttersnews.com/tablo-announces-a-new-4th-gen-ota-dvr/" >CordCuttersNews <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-format="autorelaxed"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="1223367746"></ins></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="8358498916"     data-ad-format="auto"     data-full-width-responsive="true"></ins></p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;Expanding-Viewership-Tablo-Introduces-Enhanced-OTA-DVR-with-Impressive-8TB-Capacity&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#Expanding-Viewership-Tablo-Introduces</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="tech" scheme="https://media-tips.techidaily.com/categories/tech/"/>
    
    
    <category term="streaming" scheme="https://media-tips.techidaily.com/tags/streaming/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>The End of an Era: How Plex Steps Back From Its Venture in VR Technology</title>
    <link href="https://media-tips.techidaily.com/the-end-of-an-era-how-plex-steps-back-from-its-venture-in-vr-technology/"/>
    <id>https://media-tips.techidaily.com/the-end-of-an-era-how-plex-steps-back-from-its-venture-in-vr-technology/</id>
    <published>2024-08-28T15:56:22.000Z</published>
    <updated>2024-08-29T02:27:57.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="The-End-of-an-Era-How-Plex-Steps-Back-From-Its-Venture-in-VR-Technology"><a href="#The-End-of-an-Era-How-Plex-Steps-Back-From-Its-Venture-in-VR-Technology" class="headerlink" title="The End of an Era: How Plex Steps Back From Its Venture in VR Technology"></a>The End of an Era: How Plex Steps Back From Its Venture in VR Technology</h2><p>Plex is one of the best ways to stream your own movies, TV, and music collections across all your devices. There are Plex apps for nearly every device imaginable, but now Plex is dropping support for VR platforms.</p><p> Plex announced in a forum post that it is ending support for its Google Daydream, Gear VR, and Oculus Go apps. The company said, “We recognize that this impacts several of you greatly, and we apologize for any inconvenience it will cause. This decision was not made lightly, and overall low usage played a major role in our decision process. Additionally, these platforms are either currently not, or soon will not be, supported by their manufacturers.”</p><p> Google Daydream was Google’s phone-based VR platform, <a class="link"   href="https://blog.google/products/google-ar-vr/daydream-view-coming-stores-november-10th/" >initially released in 2016 <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>. You could put your phone inside the Daydream View headset to watch videos, use a few apps, and play some games, using the phone’s processing power and display. Google stopped certifying new devices for Daydream in 2019, and only a handful of phones were ever supported.</p><p><a class="link"   href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Samsung%5FGear%5FVR" >Gear VR <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> was Samsung’s early VR platform, dating back to 2014, using the same smartphone-in-headset approach. It was developed in collaboration with Oculus, which went on to create the Oculus Go, which was a standalone headset that didn’t need an attached smartphone (but was still based on Android hardware and software).</p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static1.howtogeekimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/plex-vr-simpsons-watch-together-1-1440x810.png"                      alt="VR avatars watching The Simpsons on a large screen in a virtual living room."                > </p><p><a class="link"   href="https://www.plex.tv/blog/plex-now-virtual-reality-daydream/" >Plex <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><p> Plex had an application available for all three platforms, allowing you to watch your movies and TV shows in a virtual theater, including with friends over voice chat. It’s not surprising that support is going away for these old platforms, but Plex doesn’t support newer virtual reality devices either. There’s no Plex app for Meta Quest headsets, PC VR, or PlayStation VR. You can use the Plex web app in the web browser on Quest headsets, or mirror a PC’s screen to your headset, but that’s not the best experience.</p><p> The old apps will continue working for the moment, but they will not be available for download, and “future system updates” could break access to Plex libraries from the VR apps. Here’s hoping Plex eventually releases a new app for modern VR headsets.</p><p> Source: <a class="link"   href="https://forums.plex.tv/t/support-ending-for-google-daydream-gear-vr-oculus-go-apps/872566" >Plex <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-format="autorelaxed"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="1223367746"></ins></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="8358498916"     data-ad-format="auto"     data-full-width-responsive="true"></ins></p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;The-End-of-an-Era-How-Plex-Steps-Back-From-Its-Venture-in-VR-Technology&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#The-End-of-an-Era-How-Plex-Steps-Back-From-Its-Ve</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="tech" scheme="https://media-tips.techidaily.com/categories/tech/"/>
    
    
    <category term="streaming" scheme="https://media-tips.techidaily.com/tags/streaming/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Rewind Live Broadcasts Easily: Discover the Power of NBCUniversal&#39;s Now Service and NextGen TV Technology</title>
    <link href="https://media-tips.techidaily.com/rewind-live-broadcasts-easily-discover-the-power-of-nbcuniversals-now-service-and-nextgen-tv-technology/"/>
    <id>https://media-tips.techidaily.com/rewind-live-broadcasts-easily-discover-the-power-of-nbcuniversals-now-service-and-nextgen-tv-technology/</id>
    <published>2024-08-28T15:54:54.000Z</published>
    <updated>2024-08-29T04:43:22.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="Rewind-Live-Broadcasts-Easily-Discover-the-Power-of-NBCUniversal’s-Now-Service-and-NextGen-TV-Technology"><a href="#Rewind-Live-Broadcasts-Easily-Discover-the-Power-of-NBCUniversal’s-Now-Service-and-NextGen-TV-Technology" class="headerlink" title="Rewind Live Broadcasts Easily: Discover the Power of NBCUniversal’s Now Service and NextGen TV Technology"></a>Rewind Live Broadcasts Easily: Discover the Power of NBCUniversal’s Now Service and NextGen TV Technology</h2><p>NBCUniversal now provides enhanced personalization and rewind functionality for select OTA TV channels. This is a major landmark for broadcast television, as it’s the first real-world implementation of advanced NextGen TV functionality.</p><p> The <a class="link"   href="https://tech-haven.techidaily.com/ai-writing-unmasked-5-must-have-detectors-for-academic-and-corporate-leaders/" >NextGen TV standard <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> (ATSC 3.0) promises to deliver 4K HDR over-the-air broadcasts with enhanced streaming-like functionality. Customers can access NextGen TV broadcasts for free with an <a class="link"   href="https://www.amazon.com/SiliconDust-HDHomeRun-Flex-ATSC-NextGen/dp/B092GCN9NL?tag=hotoge-20&ascsubtag=UUhtgUeUpU2002720&asc_refurl=https://www.howtogeek.com/nbcu-lets-you-rewind-ota-channels-nextgen-tv/&asc_campaign=Short-Term" >ATSC 3.0 tuner <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> and any old <a class="link"   href="https://www.amazon.com/Amplified-Indoor-Digital-Antenna-Amplifier/dp/B0CW6NFJBS/?tag=hotoge-20&ascsubtag=UUhtgUeUpU2002720&asc_refurl=https://www.howtogeek.com/nbcu-lets-you-rewind-ota-channels-nextgen-tv/&asc_campaign=Short-Term" >TV antenna <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>. Now, six NBCU-owned stations are taking advantage of NextGen TV. Viewers can rewind or pause these channels in real-time. The channels will also show localized news or weather pop-ups, provide targeted emergency alerts, and offer viewers a selection of on-demand content.</p><p> These features work automatically for any viewer with an ATSC 3.0 tuner. However, NBCU’s rollout only impacts NBC and Telemundo channels in four markets—New York (WNBC, WNJU), Los Angeles (KNBC), Philadelphia (WCAU), and Miami (WTVJ, WSCV). And, of course, interactive elements on OTA channels will be leveraged for data collection and targeted ads.</p><p>Close </p><p> NBCU considers itself a leader in NextGen TV. The proof is in the pudding—NBCU is now the first broadcaster to introduce “personalization, hyper-localization and enhanced content capabilities” to over-the-air channels. It’s a landmark move, a proof of concept for NextGen TV’s capabilities, and a reminder that NextGen TV can be more than just “free 4K TV.”</p><p> Unfortunately, the NextGen TV rollout has been <a class="link"   href="https://techidaily.com/solutions-to-restore-deleted-files-from-tecno-by-fonelab-android-recover-data/" >extremely slow <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>. Manufacturers refuse to sell TVs with built-in ATSC 3.0 tuners, broadcasters haven’t transitioned to 4K, and most people are completely unaware of NextGen TV. Not to mention, the FCC requires extended support for legacy ATSC 1.0 channels, thereby limiting the amount of bandwidth available to ATSC 3.0 broadcasts.</p><p> And while NBCU’s actions are exciting, this is a clear sign of NextGen TV’s obscurity. The FCC has failed to educate viewers or push the market toward total ATSC 3.0 adoption, leaving broadcasters, journalists, and influencers to pick up the slack. It’s a far cry from the analog-to-digital transition of the 2000s—back then, manufacturers were forced to install digital tuners in TVs, the U.S. government handed out free digital tuner set-top boxes, and viewers were regularly informed of the switch to digital.</p><p> To reiterate, advanced NextGen TV functionality is currently limited to NBC and Telemundo stations in just four markets. NBCU says that a wider rollout will occur over the coming months.</p><p> Source: NBCU via <a class="link"   href="https://www.nexttv.com/news/nbcu-using-nextgen-tv-to-provide-personalized-broadcasts-at-6-stations" >NextTV <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-format="autorelaxed"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="1223367746"></ins></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="8358498916"     data-ad-format="auto"     data-full-width-responsive="true"></ins></p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;Rewind-Live-Broadcasts-Easily-Discover-the-Power-of-NBCUniversal’s-Now-Service-and-NextGen-TV-Technology&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#Rewind-Live-Broa</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="tech" scheme="https://media-tips.techidaily.com/categories/tech/"/>
    
    
    <category term="streaming" scheme="https://media-tips.techidaily.com/tags/streaming/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Potential Phasing Out: The Future of Roku Streambar Pro in Question</title>
    <link href="https://media-tips.techidaily.com/potential-phasing-out-the-future-of-roku-streambar-pro-in-question/"/>
    <id>https://media-tips.techidaily.com/potential-phasing-out-the-future-of-roku-streambar-pro-in-question/</id>
    <published>2024-08-28T15:51:51.000Z</published>
    <updated>2024-08-29T03:33:35.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="Potential-Phasing-Out-The-Future-of-Roku-Streambar-Pro-in-Question"><a href="#Potential-Phasing-Out-The-Future-of-Roku-Streambar-Pro-in-Question" class="headerlink" title="Potential Phasing Out: The Future of Roku Streambar Pro in Question"></a>Potential Phasing Out: The Future of Roku Streambar Pro in Question</h2><p>The Streambar Pro has been seemingly discontinued. The device is unavailable to order from Roku’s online store, and third-party retailers like Best Buy show limited stock.</p><p> Roku hasn’t officially announced the Strembar Pro’s demise, but as of the time of writing, the <a class="link"   href="https://shop-links.co/link/?exclusive=1&publisher_slug=itechdaily19598&url=https://www.bestbuy.com/site/roku-streambar-pro-4k-streaming-media-player-cinematic-audio-voice-remote-tv-controls-and-headphone-mode-black/6455163.p?skuId=6455163" >Best Buy listing <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> shows no stock available online, and Roku’s own online store redirects to the product page for the regular Streambar. It’s <a class="link"   href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B08ZJ384PP/?tag=hotoge-20&ascsubtag=UUhtgUeUpU2004825&asc_refurl=https://www.howtogeek.com/roku-streambar-pro-going-away/&asc_campaign=Short-Term" >still available on Amazon <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>, but shipping times have slipped into September. We’ve reached out to Roku to confirm, and we will update this article when we hear back.</p><p> With this change, the company offers two Streambar-branded accessories, the $80 Streambar SE and the standard $130 Streambar. Both integrate soundbar functions and a built-in 4K HDR streaming into a sleek device. The difference is that the Streambar SE ships with a standard Roku remote in the box instead of a Voice Remote and lacks support for Dolby sound and HDR10+ video (which has up to four times the peak brightness of regular HDR).</p><p> The Streambar Pro was <a class="link"   href="https://instagram-video-files.techidaily.com/new-2024-approved-designing-engaging-instagram-feature-film-posts/" >released in April 2021 <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> as an updated version of Roku’s Smart Soundbar from 2020. Both were priced the same at $180, but the Streambar Pro had four speakers, supported the Virtual Surround feature of the Roku OS, and came bundled with a Voice Remote featuring personal shortcut buttons and private listening instead of Roku’s standard remote. Roku discontinued the Smart Soundbar when the Streambar Pro went on sale.</p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static1.howtogeekimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/f117d052.jpg"                      alt="Roku Voice Remote Pro"                > </p><p> It’s unclear whether Roku plans to unveil a Streambar Pro successor anytime soon. So, what are prospective Streambar Pro buyers supposed to do now? Well, the Streambar SE and Streambar work with Roku’s Wireless Speakers and Wireless Bass, so that could be a path forward for folks who want the Streambar Pro for its immersive surround sound.</p><p> Roku’s extensive media player lineup includes four other players: the $20 Express as the cheapest Roku; the $30 Express 4K+ which upgrades video resolution to 4K HDR and brings more storage and dual-band Wi-Fi support; the $35 Streaming Stick 4K that plugs directly into your TV’s HDMI port and the $90 Ultra as the flagship option.</p><p> Source: <a class="link"   href="https://cordcuttersnews.com/roku-maybe-discontinuing-the-streambar-pro-its-soundbar-streaming-player/" >Cord Cutters News <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-format="autorelaxed"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="1223367746"></ins></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="8358498916"     data-ad-format="auto"     data-full-width-responsive="true"></ins></p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;Potential-Phasing-Out-The-Future-of-Roku-Streambar-Pro-in-Question&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#Potential-Phasing-Out-The-Future-of-Roku-Streambar-Pro</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="tech" scheme="https://media-tips.techidaily.com/categories/tech/"/>
    
    
    <category term="streaming" scheme="https://media-tips.techidaily.com/tags/streaming/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>How to Effortlessly Reduce and Monitor Your Video Platform Expenses: A Step-by-Step Guide</title>
    <link href="https://media-tips.techidaily.com/how-to-effortlessly-reduce-and-monitor-your-video-platform-expenses-a-step-by-step-guide/"/>
    <id>https://media-tips.techidaily.com/how-to-effortlessly-reduce-and-monitor-your-video-platform-expenses-a-step-by-step-guide/</id>
    <published>2024-08-28T15:32:27.000Z</published>
    <updated>2024-08-29T04:52:36.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="How-to-Effortlessly-Reduce-and-Monitor-Your-Video-Platform-Expenses-A-Step-by-Step-Guide"><a href="#How-to-Effortlessly-Reduce-and-Monitor-Your-Video-Platform-Expenses-A-Step-by-Step-Guide" class="headerlink" title="How to Effortlessly Reduce and Monitor Your Video Platform Expenses: A Step-by-Step Guide"></a>How to Effortlessly Reduce and Monitor Your Video Platform Expenses: A Step-by-Step Guide</h2><h3 id="Quick-Links"><a href="#Quick-Links" class="headerlink" title="Quick Links"></a>Quick Links</h3><ul><li><a class="link"   href="https://instagram-videos.techidaily.com/updated-avoiding-instagrams-false-facade-for-a-solid-stature-for-2024/" >Download Free Streaming Apps <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></li><li><a class="link"   href="https://android-unlock.techidaily.com/in-2024-how-to-unlock-samsung-galaxy-a54-5g-phone-without-google-account-by-drfone-android/" >Stream Free Movies With a Library Card <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></li><li><a class="link"   href="https://buynow-tips.techidaily.com/upgrading-made-simple-the-ios-15-guidebook/" >Rotate Streaming Services <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></li><li><a class="link"   href="https://extra-guidance.techidaily.com/new-quick-tips-for-transforming-pinterest-videos-into-mp3s/" >Take Advantage of Streaming Deals <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></li><li><a class="link"   href="https://some-approaches.techidaily.com/the-ultimate-setup-guide-for-effective-after-effects-texting-for-2024/" >Streaming Service Bundles <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></li><li><a class="link"   href="https://fox-glue.techidaily.com/updated-comprehensive-review-analyzing-androids-lightroom/" >Watch Free Local Channels With an Antenna <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></li><li><a class="link"   href="https://facebook-video-footage.techidaily.com/new-direct-hit-the-techno-friendly-way-to-upload-your-short-clips-for-2024/" >Refer Friends and Get Bill Credits <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></li></ul><p> Like death and taxes, streaming service price hikes have become an inevitable part of life. With this in mind, it’s wise to find ways to keep your subscription spending under control. I’ve found some ways to cut back on streaming services and actually save money by cutting the cord from cable.</p><h2 id="Download-Free-Streaming-Apps"><a href="#Download-Free-Streaming-Apps" class="headerlink" title="Download Free Streaming Apps"></a>Download Free Streaming Apps</h2><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static1.howtogeekimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/76cfbb8b-1.jpg"                      alt="Pluto TV logo on a smart TV"                > </p><p>Jordan Gloor &#x2F; How-To Geek</p><p> There was a time period when free streaming apps had clunky interfaces that were mostly littered with bargain-bin movies and annoying ads. Each time I come back to some of the <a class="link"   href="https://android-transfer.techidaily.com/how-to-transfer-data-from-samsung-galaxy-a14-5g-to-blackberry-drfone-by-drfone-transfer-from-android-transfer-from-android/" >free streaming services like Amazon Freevee and Tubi <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>, however, I’m impressed at just how far they’ve come.</p><p> You’ll find major Hollywood blockbusters from studios like Disney, Warner Bros, and Paramount that you can watch for free without having to pay a cent. In fact, I’ve noticed a pretty significant overlap between some of the paid services and their free counterparts.</p><p> Pluto TV has some of the most popular movies from Paramount+, like (at the time of publication) the first four Indiana Jones films, Sonic the Hedgehog, and Rocketman. Tubi has not only big shows from Fox (their parent company) but also, surprisingly, a sizable chunk of shows that were previously on <a class="link"   href="https://vimeo-videos.techidaily.com/new-in-2024-expert-insights-optimized-video-downloading-software/" >Max <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>, like Lovecraft Country and Batwoman. At the time of publication, several Prime Video shows are also available to watch on Amazon Freevee “for a limited time.”</p><p> You’ll also find a growing selection of live local news and even some live sports that are popping up on these free apps, too. One has to wonder, why pay for so many streaming services when you can watch all of this for free?</p><p> The trade-off with all of the free streaming services I’ve mentioned so far, though, is sitting through advertising. It varies by app, but I find that the amount of advertising for most of the major free streaming services is generally tolerable, especially with my current go-to app, Tubi.</p><p> Don’t want to sit through ads? Rest assured, there are some ways to watch free movies and shows with no advertising. That brings me to what I consider to be one of the best-kept secrets in streaming.</p><h2 id="Stream-Free-Movies-With-a-Library-Card"><a href="#Stream-Free-Movies-With-a-Library-Card" class="headerlink" title="Stream Free Movies With a Library Card"></a>Stream Free Movies With a Library Card</h2><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static1.howtogeekimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/kanopy-homepage.png"                      alt="Screenshot of the homepage on Kanopy&#39;s website on a desktop computer."                > </p><p> Two apps allow you to stream free movies and shows with no ads whatsoever, all thanks to a system of public libraries and universities. The first is called Kanopy. This free streaming service offers classic films, indie favorites, and documentaries. If you’re a fan of A24, you’ll find a wide selection of their movies through Kanopy alongside classes from The Great Courses.</p><p> To access Kanopy, you’ll need to log in with an account from a participating library or university. You can <a class="link"   href="http://www.kanopy.com/en/signup" >check to see if your library participates with Kanopy <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>.</p><p> Once you’ve logged in, you’ll get a certain number of tickets per month that you can exchange for movies. This allowance varies by library but resets at the start of every month. Kids content doesn’t require tickets.</p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static1.howtogeekimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/hoopla-homepage.png"                      alt="Screenshot of the homepage for Hoopla&#39;s website on a desktop computer."                > </p><p> The second app that allows you to stream free movies without ads is called Hoopla. They have a similar setup where you log in with a library account. A neat thing about Hoopla is they also offer audiobooks, comic books, and music that you can “borrow” through their app. Similar to Kanopy’s tickets, you get an allowance of borrows that resets each month, depending on your library.</p><p> Hoopla also offers BingePasses, which are week-long periods to access additional streaming services like CuriosityStream and Hallmark Movies Now. You can easily <a class="link"   href="http://www.hoopladigital.com/register" >see if your library participates with Hoopla <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>.</p><h2 id="Rotate-Streaming-Services"><a href="#Rotate-Streaming-Services" class="headerlink" title="Rotate Streaming Services"></a>Rotate Streaming Services</h2><p> Another way I keep my streaming service bills in check is by rotating my streaming services. Seriously, you don’t need to sign up for everything at once.</p><p> When there’s a new movie or TV show I want to watch that requires a new streaming service, I go ahead and cancel something I’m currently subscribed to. Some streaming services, like Hulu, also give you the option to pause your subscription and automatically resume at a later date.</p><p> For sports fans, this is particularly useful as you can subscribe to a live TV streaming service during a sports season and then cancel during the off-season. That’s something you wouldn’t be able to do with a cable service that has a long-term contract.</p><h2 id="Take-Advantage-of-Streaming-Deals"><a href="#Take-Advantage-of-Streaming-Deals" class="headerlink" title="Take Advantage of Streaming Deals"></a>Take Advantage of Streaming Deals</h2><p> Almost every major streaming service offers promotional discounts at least once a year. The best time to look out for deals is Black Friday, but Prime Day, the start of the NFL season, and National Streaming Day (May 20th) are good times to look for deals, too. For the past few years, I’ve signed up for streaming services like Peacock and Hulu on Black Friday and have gotten some really steep savings.</p><p> Typically, streaming deals will be offered to new customers only, but if you’re a current customer, there are some workarounds. For example, if you try to cancel your current subscription, you might be offered promotional pricing as a retention offer (I’ve gotten deals this way with Max and STARZ).</p><p> You can also try canceling your subscription and then signing up for a new account with a different email address and payment information.</p><p> Here are some other types of discounts to be aware of:</p><ul><li><strong>Student discounts</strong>: If you’re a college student, you can get discounts from services including Paramount+, Peacock, Hulu, and Amazon Prime.</li><li><strong>Cellular providers:</strong> Customers for companies like Verizon and T-Mobile can get discounts (or even free memberships) on streaming services like The Disney Bundle and Apple TV+.</li><li><strong>Annual plans:</strong> Some streaming services offer discounts if pay for an entire year upfront instead of getting billed monthly.</li></ul><h2 id="Streaming-Service-Bundles"><a href="#Streaming-Service-Bundles" class="headerlink" title="Streaming Service Bundles"></a>Streaming Service Bundles</h2><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static1.howtogeekimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/799bad5a-5.jpg"                      alt="The Disney Bundle promotional page"                > </p><p>Disney</p><p> A growing number of streaming services offer “bundle” options. This consolidates multiple services into one bill that is also lower in cost than if you were to purchase the services separately. I’ve gotten bundles through my cell phone provider, Verizon, which has helped me cut back on expenses.</p><p> Here are some of the most popular bundles at the time of publication in July 2024:</p><ul><li><strong>The Disney Bundle:</strong> Disney’s streaming services (Disney+, Hulu, and ESPN+) are offered in various bundle combinations. Later this year, they also plan to offer a bundle with Disney+, Hulu, and Max.</li><li><strong>StreamSaver Bundle</strong>: Xfinity Internet customers can get a bundle that includes Apple TV+, Netflix (ad supported), and Peacock (ad supported) for $15&#x2F;month.</li><li><strong>Verizon Bundles</strong>: Verizon customers can get various streaming deals, including a bundle with Netflix and Max for $10&#x2F;month (both are the ad-supported plans).</li></ul><h2 id="Watch-Free-Local-Channels-With-an-Antenna"><a href="#Watch-Free-Local-Channels-With-an-Antenna" class="headerlink" title="Watch Free Local Channels With an Antenna"></a>Watch Free Local Channels With an Antenna</h2><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static1.howtogeekimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/tablo-4th-gen-5.jpg"                      alt="Holding a TV antenna from Tablo 4th Gen"                > </p><p>Corbin Davenport &#x2F; How-To Geek</p><p> Despite a switch to a digital signal, this is something that hasn’t changed since the dawn of television. You can still <a class="link"   href="https://sound-issues.techidaily.com/how-to-fix-a-non-functioning-steelseries-arctis-pro-microphone-complete-solution/" >plug an antenna into a TV and watch local channels for free <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>. The rollout of NextGen TV also means you can get nifty new features like the ability <a class="link"   href="https://instagram-clips.techidaily.com/updated-unleash-a-flood-of-supporters-attain-a-million-ish-on-ig-each-month-for-2024/" >to pause and rewind certain over-the-air channels <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>.</p><p> With an antenna, I get dozens of local channels like CBS, FOX, ABC, and NBC, all without paying anything. For comparison, the cheapest live TV streaming service to include the big four broadcasters is YouTube TV, which costs $73 a month. Plus, with an over-the-air DVR like the ones from Tablo and AirTV. I’ve been able to record shows and cast them on other devices.</p><h2 id="Refer-Friends-and-Get-Bill-Credits"><a href="#Refer-Friends-and-Get-Bill-Credits" class="headerlink" title="Refer Friends and Get Bill Credits"></a>Refer Friends and Get Bill Credits</h2><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static1.howtogeekimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/fubo-refer-a-friend.png"                      alt="Screenshot of a form on Fubo&#39;s website where you can invite friends to get $30 off your bill."                > </p><p> If you subscribe to certain live TV services like YouTube TV or Fubo, you can save some money by referring friends and family. If you share your referral code with someone else and they enter it when checking out, you’ll both get a bill credit. So it’s a win-win! I’ve gotten some huge discounts on YouTube TV this way.</p><hr><p> So yes, streaming has gotten more expensive (and its price continues to go up!), but with these tips, you can cut back on those dreaded bills just like I did.</p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-format="autorelaxed"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="1223367746"></ins></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="8358498916"     data-ad-format="auto"     data-full-width-responsive="true"></ins></p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;How-to-Effortlessly-Reduce-and-Monitor-Your-Video-Platform-Expenses-A-Step-by-Step-Guide&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#How-to-Effortlessly-Reduce-and-M</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="tech" scheme="https://media-tips.techidaily.com/categories/tech/"/>
    
    
    <category term="streaming" scheme="https://media-tips.techidaily.com/tags/streaming/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Revolutionize Your Home Screen with This Simple Google TV Upgrade</title>
    <link href="https://media-tips.techidaily.com/revolutionize-your-home-screen-with-this-simple-google-tv-upgrade/"/>
    <id>https://media-tips.techidaily.com/revolutionize-your-home-screen-with-this-simple-google-tv-upgrade/</id>
    <published>2024-08-28T15:26:27.000Z</published>
    <updated>2024-08-29T02:40:36.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="Revolutionize-Your-Home-Screen-with-This-Simple-Google-TV-Upgrade"><a href="#Revolutionize-Your-Home-Screen-with-This-Simple-Google-TV-Upgrade" class="headerlink" title="Revolutionize Your Home Screen with This Simple Google TV Upgrade"></a>Revolutionize Your Home Screen with This Simple Google TV Upgrade</h2><h3 id="Key-Takeaways"><a href="#Key-Takeaways" class="headerlink" title="Key Takeaways"></a>Key Takeaways</h3><ul><li>Google TV’s Apps Only Mode removes recommendations for a cleaner home screen.</li><li>This mode now features a grid layout of installed apps instead of a single row.</li><li>Enabling Apps Only Mode simplifies navigation but disables content search and Google Assistant.</li></ul><p> There’s no denying that the Google TV home screen is stuffed to the brim with recommendations. While some of this stuff may be useful, much of it feels like glorified ads. The good news is there’s a simple toggle you can enable to remove most of the junk and put your apps front and center.</p><p> Since the beginning, <a class="link"   href="https://fake-location.techidaily.com/wondering-the-best-alternative-to-hola-on-apple-iphone-6s-plus-here-is-the-answer-drfone-by-drfone-virtual-ios/" >Google TV devices <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> have included a little-known feature called “Apps Only Mode.” As the name implies, Apps Only Mode strips away everything on the home screen except the installed apps. That includes the “Top Picks For You” section, the “Continue Watching” row, and even the “Live” and “Library” tabs at the top of the screen.</p><p> The one thing that remains is the big “Highlights” carousel at the top of the screen. However, <a class="link"   href="https://tech-haven.techidaily.com/unlocking-conversational-ai-in-linux-connecting-chatgpt-to-the-ubuntu-shell/" >since we last talked about this feature <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>, Apps Only Mode has been redesigned. You now get a grid of nice big, rectangle icons rather than a single side-scrolling row. It’s pretty nice.</p><p> Apps Only Mode disables the content search feature and Google Assistant.</p><p> To enable Apps Only Mode, select the gear icon in the top right corner of the home screen, then select the “Settings” gear again from the menu.</p><p>Close </p><p> Now go to Accounts &amp; Sign In &gt; Your Account. Toggle on “Apps Only Mode” and confirm your selection on the following screen.</p><p>Close </p><p> Here’s the before and after!</p><p>Close </p><p> If you primarily just open apps on your Google TV device—and let’s be honest, that’s what most of us do—this is a much more direct and simplified way to navigate your TV. It’s a bummer that you can’t use Google Assistant in Apps Only Mode, but that may be a sacrifice worth taking.</p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-format="autorelaxed"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="1223367746"></ins></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="8358498916"     data-ad-format="auto"     data-full-width-responsive="true"></ins></p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;Revolutionize-Your-Home-Screen-with-This-Simple-Google-TV-Upgrade&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#Revolutionize-Your-Home-Screen-with-This-Simple-Google-</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="tech" scheme="https://media-tips.techidaily.com/categories/tech/"/>
    
    
    <category term="streaming" scheme="https://media-tips.techidaily.com/tags/streaming/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Unlocking Spotify&#39;s Growth: An Increase in Visual Soundbite Series Awaits You</title>
    <link href="https://media-tips.techidaily.com/unlocking-spotifys-growth-an-increase-in-visual-soundbite-series-awaits-you/"/>
    <id>https://media-tips.techidaily.com/unlocking-spotifys-growth-an-increase-in-visual-soundbite-series-awaits-you/</id>
    <published>2024-08-28T15:23:56.000Z</published>
    <updated>2024-08-29T02:49:54.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="Unlocking-Spotify’s-Growth-An-Increase-in-Visual-Soundbite-Series-Awaits-You"><a href="#Unlocking-Spotify’s-Growth-An-Increase-in-Visual-Soundbite-Series-Awaits-You" class="headerlink" title="Unlocking Spotify’s Growth: An Increase in Visual Soundbite Series Awaits You"></a>Unlocking Spotify’s Growth: An Increase in Visual Soundbite Series Awaits You</h2><p>The important part of podcasts is the audio and the conversation that’s going on, but some shows have video versions you can watch, too. Spotify allowed podcast hosts to upload video, but until now, only some hand-picked podcasts could do it. Now, Spotify is opening the feature up to all creators.</p><p> In a move to further boost its video <a class="link"   href="https://review-topics.techidaily.com/how-to-changefake-your-vivo-y200e-5g-location-on-viber-drfone-by-drfone-virtual-android/" >podcast <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> offerings, Spotify has quietly rolled out a new feature allowing all podcast creators to upload video content directly to the platform, regardless of their hosting provider. Previously, this option was limited to creators using Spotify for Podcasters or specific partner platforms. The end result is that you might start seeing more podcasts with video versions on Spotify, especially for shows that already have video versions on YouTube or other platforms, now that the option is available to all podcasters on Spotify.</p><p> The new feature simplifies the process for creators, who can now easily add video versions to their existing audio-only episodes through the Spotify for Podcasters portal. Podcasts can still be audio-only, though, it’s not a requirement. Likewise, as a listener, you can also choose to just listen to the podcast instead of watching it.</p><p> What is clear is that the company <em>really</em> wants creators to upload video to their podcasts. Over 250,000 video podcasts have been uploaded to the platform, a substantial increase from 100,000 in 2023. With video podcasts now being open to basically all creators, this number will likely grow exponenntially. The company also shared that over 170 million users globally are engaging with video podcasts on Spotify, with a 40% year-over-year increase in monthly active viewers. Spotify is definitely pitching this as a way for shows to get more attention.</p><p> Video podcasts have been available through the Spotify app for a while, and you don’t need to do anything to see the videos from these new creators. If you don’t like the videos, you can just ignore them and keep listening to the audio in the background, or use a different app for podcasts like Pocket Casts or <a class="link"   href="https://video-capture.techidaily.com/new-2024-approved-navigating-the-world-of-zooms-camera-snapping-easily/" >Apple Podcasts <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>.</p><p> Source: <a class="link"   href="https://podnews.net/update/spotify-video-all-podcasts" >PodNews <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>, <a class="link"   href="https://techcrunch.com/2024/06/20/spotify-surpasses-250000-video-podcast-shows/" >TechCrunch <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-format="autorelaxed"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="1223367746"></ins></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="8358498916"     data-ad-format="auto"     data-full-width-responsive="true"></ins></p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;Unlocking-Spotify’s-Growth-An-Increase-in-Visual-Soundbite-Series-Awaits-You&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#Unlocking-Spotify’s-Growth-An-Increase-in-Vi</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="tech" scheme="https://media-tips.techidaily.com/categories/tech/"/>
    
    
    <category term="streaming" scheme="https://media-tips.techidaily.com/tags/streaming/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Enjoy Your Favorite Films and Shows Anywhere with Step-by-Step Tips on Securely Downloading Content for Offline Use</title>
    <link href="https://media-tips.techidaily.com/enjoy-your-favorite-films-and-shows-anywhere-with-step-by-step-tips-on-securely-downloading-content-for-offline-use/"/>
    <id>https://media-tips.techidaily.com/enjoy-your-favorite-films-and-shows-anywhere-with-step-by-step-tips-on-securely-downloading-content-for-offline-use/</id>
    <published>2024-08-28T15:20:24.000Z</published>
    <updated>2024-08-29T02:33:24.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="Enjoy-Your-Favorite-Films-and-Shows-Anywhere-with-Step-by-Step-Tips-on-Securely-Downloading-Content-for-Offline-Use"><a href="#Enjoy-Your-Favorite-Films-and-Shows-Anywhere-with-Step-by-Step-Tips-on-Securely-Downloading-Content-for-Offline-Use" class="headerlink" title="Enjoy Your Favorite Films and Shows Anywhere with Step-by-Step Tips on Securely Downloading Content for Offline Use"></a>Enjoy Your Favorite Films and Shows Anywhere with Step-by-Step Tips on Securely Downloading Content for Offline Use</h2><h3 id="Quick-Links"><a href="#Quick-Links" class="headerlink" title="Quick Links"></a>Quick Links</h3><ul><li><a class="link"   href="https://youtube-clips.techidaily.com/unlocking-youtube-sounds-through-screen-capture/" >Amazon Prime Video <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></li><li><a class="link"   href="https://howto.techidaily.com/intel-elevates-processing-power-with-new-optical-connectivity-standard-delivering-up-to-4tbps-data-transfer-rate-for-chiplets/" >YouTube Premium <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></li><li><a class="link"   href="https://instagram-video-files.techidaily.com/new-in-2024-7-proven-strategies-for-astonishing-ig-films/" >Netflix <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></li><li><a class="link"   href="https://some-techniques.techidaily.com/in-2024-front-seat-escapades-beyond-athletic-viewing/" >Hulu <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></li><li><a class="link"   href="https://youtube-clips.techidaily.com/cutting-edge-professional-guide-to-youtube-editing/" >Disney+ <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></li><li><a class="link"   href="https://www.howtogeek.com/262480/how-to-download-movies-and-tv-shows-to-watch-them-on-an-airplane-or-anywhere-else-offline/#hbo-max" >(HBO) Max <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></li><li><a class="link"   href="https://fake-location.techidaily.com/best-10-mock-location-apps-worth-trying-on-vivo-x90s-drfone-by-drfone-virtual-android/" >Rip Your Own DVDs or Blu-rays <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></li></ul><p> Solid Internet connections aren’t available everywhere. If you want to watch streaming movies and TV shows on an airplane, on the subway, or somewhere out in the wilderness away from cellular towers, you can download them ahead of time.</p><p> Not every service offers a download feature, but quite a few services allow you to download videos ahead of time so you can take them with you. This could save lots of valuable cellular data, too, especially if you’re <a class="link"   href="https://snapchat-videos.techidaily.com/new-in-2024-how-to-create-snapchat-lenses-easily-2-methods/" >roaming internationally <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>. Let’s take a look at some of your options.</p><h2 id="Amazon-Prime-Video"><a href="#Amazon-Prime-Video" class="headerlink" title="Amazon Prime Video"></a>Amazon Prime Video</h2><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static1.howtogeekimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/2024-04-26_16-27-05.png"                      alt="Amazon Prime download button."                > </p><p> The Amazon Prime Video app, available for <a class="link"   href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/links/3607085/type/dlg/sid/UUhtgUeUpU218295/https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/amazon-video/id545519333?mt=8" >iPhones and iPads <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>, <a class="link"   href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/links/3607085/type/dlg/sid/UUhtgUeUpU218295/https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.amazon.avod.thirdpartyclient&hl=en" >Android devices <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>, and Fire Tablets, allows you to download videos to your device so you can watch them offline.</p><p> Just download the app and sign in with your Amazon account. Find the movie or TV show you want to watch and tap the “Download” button to the right of it. Downloaded videos will appear in the “Downloads” section of the app later, so you can open the app and watch them—even without an Internet connection.</p><h2 id="YouTube-Premium"><a href="#YouTube-Premium" class="headerlink" title="YouTube Premium"></a>YouTube Premium</h2><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static1.howtogeekimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/2024-04-26_16-37-51.png"                      alt="YouTube download button."                > </p><p> YouTube offers this feature, but only if you pay for YouTube Premium. To download a video, open the YouTube app on an <a class="link"   href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/links/3607085/type/dlg/sid/UUhtgUeUpU218295/https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/youtube/id544007664?mt=8" >iPhone, iPad <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>, or <a class="link"   href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/links/3607085/type/dlg/sid/UUhtgUeUpU218295/https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.google.android.youtube&hl=en" >Android device <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> and look for the buttons underneath the channel name. Tap the “Download” button.</p><p> You’ll find the videos you saved for offline use under the profile tab. Tap “Downloads,” and you’ll see a list of videos you can watch offline. This feature is only available in the YouTube app for iPhones, iPads, and Android devices.</p><h2 id="Netflix"><a href="#Netflix" class="headerlink" title="Netflix"></a>Netflix</h2><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static1.howtogeekimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/2024-04-26_16-31-58.png"                      alt="Netflix download button."                > </p><p> Over on Netflix, not every single movie or TV show is available to download for offline viewing. Instead, you’ll need to go to a specific section to see what’s available. On your <a class="link"   href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/netflix/id363590051" >iPhone, iPad <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>, or <a class="link"   href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/links/3607085/type/dlg/sid/UUhtgUeUpU218295/https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.netflix.mediaclient&hl=en_US&gl=US" >Android <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>device, go to My Netflix &gt; Downloads &gt; See What You Can Download.</p><p> From here, you’ll see everything that’s available to download. Select a movie or TV show you’d like to download, then simply tap the download icon next to it. Note that for TV shows you’ll need to do this for each individual episode. Go to My Netflix &gt; Downloads to see everything you’ve downloaded.</p><h2 id="Hulu"><a href="#Hulu" class="headerlink" title="Hulu"></a>Hulu</h2><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static1.howtogeekimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/2024-04-26_16-37-01.png"                      alt="Hulu details button."                > </p><p> Can you download shows on Hulu? Yes, and movies, too. However, you need to have a Hulu plan <em>without ads</em>. To find content that can be downloaded for offline viewing, open Hulu on an <a class="link"   href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/hulu-watch-tv-shows-movies/id376510438" >iPad, iPhone <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>, or <a class="link"   href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/links/3607085/type/dlg/sid/UUhtgUeUpU218295/https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.hulu.plus&hl=en_US&gl=US" >Android <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>device and go to Downloads &gt; See What’s Downloadable.</p><p> When you find something you’d like to watch offline, tap the “Download” button on the “Details” page. For TV shows, you’ll need to do this for each episode. Hulu will ask if you want to download the content with your data connection if you aren’t connected to Wi-Fi.</p><h2 id="Disney"><a href="#Disney" class="headerlink" title="Disney+"></a>Disney+</h2><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static1.howtogeekimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/2024-04-26_16-26-26.png"                      alt="Disney+ download button."                > </p><p> Disney+ also supports downloads for offline viewing, but just like Hulu, you must have a plan that doesn’t include ads. Launch the app on your <a class="link"   href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/disney/id1446075923" >iPhone, iPad <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>, or <a class="link"   href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/links/3607085/type/dlg/sid/UUhtgUeUpU218295/https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.disney.disneyplus&hl=en_US&gl=US" >Android <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>device and navigate to something you’d like to download. Simply tap the “Download” button on the Details page.</p><p> After you’ve downloaded content, you can find it to watch offline from the “Downloads” tab.</p><h2 id="HBO-Max"><a href="#HBO-Max" class="headerlink" title="(HBO) Max"></a>(HBO) Max</h2><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static1.howtogeekimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/2024-04-26_16-30-36.png"                      alt="HBO Max download button."                > </p><p> Downloading content for offline viewing with Max (formerly HBO Max) is essentially the same as most services. Simply find something you’d like to watch in the <a class="link"   href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/max-stream-hbo-tv-movies/id1666653815" >iPhone, iPad <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>, or <a class="link"   href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/links/3607085/type/dlg/sid/UUhtgUeUpU218295/https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.wbd.stream&hl=en_US&gl=US" >Android <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>app and tap the download icon on the information page for the movie or show. For shows, you can download each episode separately.</p><p> And to watch that downlaoded content, simply go to the Downloads tab on the home page of the app.</p><h2 id="Rip-Your-Own-DVDs-or-Blu-rays"><a href="#Rip-Your-Own-DVDs-or-Blu-rays" class="headerlink" title="Rip Your Own DVDs or Blu-rays"></a>Rip Your Own DVDs or Blu-rays</h2><p> Lastly, if you have movies or TV shows on physical DVD or Blu-ray discs, you can “rip” them to digital video files you can more easily take with you. Store these files on a laptop, smartphone, or tablet, and you can watch them without taking the disc with you.</p><p> You can rip DVDs and Blu-rays with a variety of programs, but we particularly like <a class="link"   href="https://handbrake.fr/" >Handbrake <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>—it’s free and contains presets for ripping files compatible with iPhone, iPad, Android, and more.</p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-format="autorelaxed"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="1223367746"></ins></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="8358498916"     data-ad-format="auto"     data-full-width-responsive="true"></ins></p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;Enjoy-Your-Favorite-Films-and-Shows-Anywhere-with-Step-by-Step-Tips-on-Securely-Downloading-Content-for-Offline-Use&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#Enjoy</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="tech" scheme="https://media-tips.techidaily.com/categories/tech/"/>
    
    
    <category term="streaming" scheme="https://media-tips.techidaily.com/tags/streaming/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Catch Every NFL Game Live: Top 5 Essential Streaming Services for Football Fans</title>
    <link href="https://media-tips.techidaily.com/catch-every-nfl-game-live-top-5-essential-streaming-services-for-football-fans/"/>
    <id>https://media-tips.techidaily.com/catch-every-nfl-game-live-top-5-essential-streaming-services-for-football-fans/</id>
    <published>2024-08-28T15:12:21.000Z</published>
    <updated>2024-08-29T03:48:31.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="Catch-Every-NFL-Game-Live-Top-5-Essential-Streaming-Services-for-Football-Fans"><a href="#Catch-Every-NFL-Game-Live-Top-5-Essential-Streaming-Services-for-Football-Fans" class="headerlink" title="Catch Every NFL Game Live: Top 5 Essential Streaming Services for Football Fans"></a>Catch Every NFL Game Live: Top 5 Essential Streaming Services for Football Fans</h2><h3 id="Key-Takeaways"><a href="#Key-Takeaways" class="headerlink" title="Key Takeaways"></a>Key Takeaways</h3><ul><li>More NFL games are moving to streaming services, with multiple games exclusively on platforms like Peacock, Netflix, and Amazon Prime Video.</li><li>To stream all NFL games in the 2024-25 season, fans will need to subscribe to at least five services and spend hundreds of dollars.</li><li>The days of simply using cable TV to watch football are gone, with fans now needing to juggle multiple apps and subscriptions to catch all the action.</li></ul><p> Do you miss regular cable TV yet? I certainly do. NFL fans will have difficulty watching games for the upcoming 2024-25 NFL season because many will air exclusively on streaming services. What a mess.</p><p> If you thought it was <a class="link"   href="https://win-blog.techidaily.com/fixes-and-solutions-stop-valheim-from-lagging-or-freezing-on-your-computer/" >complicated and expensive a few years ago <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>, things are about to get worse. Even with cable or satellite, you’ll have to spend hundreds of dollars on at least four different apps and streaming services to catch all the big games this year.</p><p> Sling TV and YouTube TV might be a cable replacement, but they are still fundamentally subscription streaming services. So without a traditional cable or similar you’re up to a minimum of five: YouTube TV or Sling TV, plus Peacock, Netflix, Prime Video, and ESPN+.</p><p> Without those core five, you’re in for an even bigger mess. Potentially, you might need up to ten different apps and streaming services just to watch all the games. Here’s why.</p><h2 id="The-NFL-Is-All-In-on-Streaming"><a href="#The-NFL-Is-All-In-on-Streaming" class="headerlink" title="The NFL Is All-In on Streaming"></a>The NFL Is All-In on Streaming</h2><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static1.howtogeekimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/nfl-on-netflix.jpg"                      alt="NFL only on Netflix for Christmas 2024."                > </p><p>Netflix &#x2F; NFL</p><p> The NFL is officially all-in on streaming services, even if that negatively affects fans. Gone are the days of using cable TV to watch football or getting the NFL Sunday Ticket from DirecTV. The only way to get the <a class="link"   href="https://digital-screen-recording.techidaily.com/complete-manual-for-expert-use-of-screen-recorder-by-zd-soft-for-2024/" >NFL Ticket is on YouTube TV <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>, which still, shockingly, doesn’t get you every game.</p><p> For example, last season, the <em>only</em> way to watch the Bills vs. Chargers in December 2023 was to subscribe to NBC’s Peacock streaming service. Making matters worse, the NFL doubled down and put the prime time January playoff game between the Dolphins and Chiefs behind Peacock, which costs $5.99 or $11.99 per month, depending on the package you get.</p><p> Fans had to sign up and subscribe to Peacock to watch the game, and <a class="link"   href="https://www.antenna.live/post/do-nfl-sign-ups-stick-around" >reports suggest <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> that over 70% of sign-ups didn’t cancel a month later. This means one game costs fans anywhere from $12-$24 to watch, if not more, for those who forgot to cancel.</p><p> For the upcoming 2024-25 NFL season, Peacock will again exclusively air the season opener between the Packers and Eagles on September 6th in Brazil, and likely others later in the year.</p><p> Then, Thursday Night Football (TNF) airs on Amazon Prime Video, with exclusive rights to air one playoff game. Now, the <a class="link"   href="https://www.netflix.com/tudum/articles/nfl-games-on-netflix" >NFL and Netflix have just announced <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> that if you want to watch the two NFL games on Christmas Day as a family, you’ll only be able to see them by subscribing to Netflix. Yes, Netflix. Plus, ESPN+ will host and air an undecided exclusive as well.</p><h2 id="Here’s-How-Much-It’ll-Cost-to-Stream-All-the-NFL-Games"><a href="#Here’s-How-Much-It’ll-Cost-to-Stream-All-the-NFL-Games" class="headerlink" title="Here’s How Much It’ll Cost to Stream All the NFL Games"></a>Here’s How Much It’ll Cost to Stream All the NFL Games</h2><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static1.howtogeekimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/peacock.jpg"                      alt="Peacock logo"                > </p><p>Corbin Davenport &#x2F; Peacock</p><p> Where does that leave the fans? If you want to watch every NFL game this upcoming season, it’ll cost you nearly a thousand dollars and require five different streaming services and apps. So much for cutting the cord; now it’s a requirement.</p><p> Most people use a streaming service like YouTube TV or Sling TV instead of cable, and that’s cool. However, then you’ll need to sign up for the NFL Sunday Ticket and subscribe to all the streaming services with exclusive rights to broadcast NFL games. Here’s how that breaks down monthly and throughout the entire season over six months:</p><ul><li><strong>YouTube TV</strong> or similar: $72.99 per month</li><li><strong>Peacock:</strong> $5.99 or $11.99 without ads</li><li><strong>Amazon Prime Video:</strong> $8.99 or $14.99</li><li><strong>ESPN+:</strong> $10.99</li><li><strong>Netflix:</strong> $6.99</li></ul><p> If you sign up and subscribe to each streaming service to enjoy the NFL between September and February, you’ll pay over $600 for six months of service. And it’ll cost even more if you choose a higher ad-free plan for Peacock or Netflix. Sure, you could cancel Peacock after those games air or Netflix after Christmas, but they’re banking you’ll forget.</p><p> Then, by adding on the NFL Sunday Ticket from YouTube, <a class="link"   href="https://tv.youtube.com/learn/nflsundayticket/" >which is $349 <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>, the total comes out to over $980 for one football season. Ouch.</p><p> Technically, if you cancel cable and don’t have YouTube TV, the situation gets worse. You’d need to download apps from ABC, CBS, ESPN, ESPN+, NBC, Peacock, Fox, NFL Network, Amazon Prime Video, and now Netflix. Just thinking about it gives me a headache.</p><p> The old days of watching NFL football are long gone. Even if you still have DirecTV, Dish, Comcast, Cox Cable, or something similar, you won’t be able to watch the games on Peacock or Netflix without downloading the app to your phone or TV, subscribing, and paying another monthly fee. Those games are exclusively airing on those services only.</p><p> If you’re looking for the easiest way to watch sports or the <a class="link"   href="https://easy-unlock-android.techidaily.com/unlock-your-poco-c65-phone-with-ease-the-3-best-lock-screen-removal-tools-by-drfone-android/" >cheapest way to stream sports <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> like the NFL, I’m not sure what to tell you anymore. But I can say this. If you’re planning to watch games with friends and family this year, especially at the holidays, you’d better do your research and make sure you’ve got the right streaming app installed on your smart TV or streaming stick first.</p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-format="autorelaxed"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="1223367746"></ins></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="8358498916"     data-ad-format="auto"     data-full-width-responsive="true"></ins></p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;Catch-Every-NFL-Game-Live-Top-5-Essential-Streaming-Services-for-Football-Fans&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#Catch-Every-NFL-Game-Live-Top-5-Essential-</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="tech" scheme="https://media-tips.techidaily.com/categories/tech/"/>
    
    
    <category term="streaming" scheme="https://media-tips.techidaily.com/tags/streaming/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>The Declining Standard of Promotions on Amazon&#39;s Fire TV Platform</title>
    <link href="https://media-tips.techidaily.com/the-declining-standard-of-promotions-on-amazons-fire-tv-platform/"/>
    <id>https://media-tips.techidaily.com/the-declining-standard-of-promotions-on-amazons-fire-tv-platform/</id>
    <published>2024-08-28T14:59:12.000Z</published>
    <updated>2024-08-29T02:40:31.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="The-Declining-Standard-of-Promotions-on-Amazon’s-Fire-TV-Platform"><a href="#The-Declining-Standard-of-Promotions-on-Amazon’s-Fire-TV-Platform" class="headerlink" title="The Declining Standard of Promotions on Amazon’s Fire TV Platform"></a>The Declining Standard of Promotions on Amazon’s Fire TV Platform</h2><p>No one likes ads, but all those big-budget movies and shows don’t pay for themselves. Streaming services and smart TV platforms have been experimenting with new types of ads, some of which are pretty annoying. If you happen to have a Fire TV device, not only will you have to put up with more ads on your streaming services of choice, but you’ll also have ads on the home screen as well.</p><p> Amazon has announced new advertising options for advertisers on Fire TV, with the company saying that it aims to let advertisers reach roughly 155 million unduplicated monthly viewers, or six out of every 10 U.S. adults, with its ads. Notably, Amazon is opening up the “Feature Rotator,” which was previously reserved only for streaming services to advertise their content, to other advertisers, so you might see ads for real-life products such as cars, snacks, and everything in between as a banner on top of your home screen. This banner basically takes half your screen, and it will also have a video component that will let the ad play a video for you — you <em>can</em> disable autoplay, at least, so it won’t straight up get loud the second it loads unless you want it to, but it’s still there.</p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static1.howtogeekimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/amazon-fire-tv-ads-2023.jpg"                      alt="Amazon Fire TV Ads 2023"                > </p><p>Amazon via StreamTV Insider</p><p> In addition to this, Amazon is also throwing in some ads on the search page, which was previously ad-free. Amazon is going to sell slots to advertisers to put “sponsored tiles” next to search results, which will be shown next to the top search result in any given query.</p><p> Google TV <a class="link"   href="https://easy-unlock-android.techidaily.com/in-2024-rootjunky-apk-to-bypass-google-frp-lock-for-realme-narzo-n55-by-drfone-android/" >took a similar step earlier this year <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>, when it yanked up the number of ads throughout the system and notably also opened up its top-banner ads to third-party advertisers. So, this seems to be a common theme by this point, and something that will likely become unescapable across most, if not all, smart TV platforms. Some platforms are still less invasive with advertising than others — Roku’s home screen is still relatively minimal for the moment — but the trend is definitely becoming more tiresome.</p><p> Source: <a class="link"   href="https://www.streamtvinsider.com/advertising/amazon-fire-tv-intros-new-options-advertisers-including-contextual-sponsored-tiles" >StreamTV Insider <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> via <a class="link"   href="https://www.techhive.com/article/2123287/fire-tv-banner-ads-are-about-to-get-worse.html" >TechHive <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-format="autorelaxed"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="1223367746"></ins></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="8358498916"     data-ad-format="auto"     data-full-width-responsive="true"></ins></p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;The-Declining-Standard-of-Promotions-on-Amazon’s-Fire-TV-Platform&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#The-Declining-Standard-of-Promotions-on-Amazon’s-Fire-T</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="tech" scheme="https://media-tips.techidaily.com/categories/tech/"/>
    
    
    <category term="streaming" scheme="https://media-tips.techidaily.com/tags/streaming/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Transforming YouTube&#39;s Audio Offerings: Essential Strategies for Enhanced Song Recommendations</title>
    <link href="https://media-tips.techidaily.com/transforming-youtubes-audio-offerings-essential-strategies-for-enhanced-song-recommendations/"/>
    <id>https://media-tips.techidaily.com/transforming-youtubes-audio-offerings-essential-strategies-for-enhanced-song-recommendations/</id>
    <published>2024-08-28T14:56:16.000Z</published>
    <updated>2024-08-29T02:55:27.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="Transforming-YouTube’s-Audio-Offerings-Essential-Strategies-for-Enhanced-Song-Recommendations"><a href="#Transforming-YouTube’s-Audio-Offerings-Essential-Strategies-for-Enhanced-Song-Recommendations" class="headerlink" title="Transforming YouTube’s Audio Offerings: Essential Strategies for Enhanced Song Recommendations"></a>Transforming YouTube’s Audio Offerings: Essential Strategies for Enhanced Song Recommendations</h2><h3 id="Quick-Links"><a href="#Quick-Links" class="headerlink" title="Quick Links"></a>Quick Links</h3><ul><li><a class="link"   href="https://some-skills.techidaily.com/in-2024-strategies-for-discerning-professional-film-making-talents/" >Improve YouTube Music Recommendations <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></li><li><a class="link"   href="https://tiktok-clips.techidaily.com/updated-2024-approved-navigate-to-connect-with-a-tiktok-life-stream/" >Continue to Dislike Songs, Videos, or Podcasts You Don’t Like <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></li><li><a class="link"   href="https://android-location-track.techidaily.com/in-2024-5-ways-to-track-itel-a60s-without-app-drfone-by-drfone-virtual-android/" >Try the Music Tuner to Create a Radio <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></li><li><a class="link"   href="https://fox-direct.techidaily.com/mastering-photomontages-a-comprehensive-guide-for-2024/" >Remove Content You Don’t Enjoy <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></li><li><a class="link"   href="https://bypass-frp.techidaily.com/hassle-free-ways-to-remove-frp-lock-on-xiaomi-redmi-12-phones-withwithout-a-pc-by-drfone-android/" >Reset the YouTube Music Algorithm <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></li></ul><p> I’m a big YouTube Music fan dating back to Google’s original Play Music subscription service. However, like anyone with Apple Music or Spotify, over the years, algorithm and song suggestions eventually started to struggle. Here’s how I fixed it and started loving YouTube Music again.</p><h2 id="Improve-YouTube-Music-Recommendations"><a href="#Improve-YouTube-Music-Recommendations" class="headerlink" title="Improve YouTube Music Recommendations"></a>Improve YouTube Music Recommendations</h2><p> When you use the same music streaming service for years, play songs for friends, take requests at a BBQ, and thumbs up&#x2F;down all sorts of content, the recommended music eventually gets a little weird.</p><p> There are countless reasons to use YouTube Music, as it’s <a class="link"   href="https://fox-cloud.techidaily.com/updated-mastering-overloaded-tiktok-saves-a-guide-to-editing-and-streamlining/" >packed with features <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>. Interestingly enough, one such feature is the option to manually improve the algorithm for suggestions and song recommendations. Here’s how:</p><p>Close </p><p> Fire up YouTube Music and tap your Profile photo in the top right corner. Select “Settings” near the bottom, tap on “Recommendations,” and hit the “Improve Your Music Recommendations” button. From here, YouTube Music will let you pick five artists you like and will automatically populate a few from your listening history. Choose specific artists if you’re looking for a certain genre or a varied mix of artists you enjoy. You’ll see a ton of bands here, so choose wisely, then select “Done” at the bottom of the screen.</p><p> Now, YouTube Music better understands your music tastes, especially if they’ve changed over the years, and can slightly retrain the algorithm. Yes, you do this when you first sign up, but after years of use, it needed another round. I did this and noticed an immediate difference.</p><h2 id="Continue-to-Dislike-Songs-Videos-or-Podcasts-You-Don’t-Like"><a href="#Continue-to-Dislike-Songs-Videos-or-Podcasts-You-Don’t-Like" class="headerlink" title="Continue to Dislike Songs, Videos, or Podcasts You Don’t Like"></a>Continue to Dislike Songs, Videos, or Podcasts You Don’t Like</h2><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static1.howtogeekimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/6b0ab20a.jpg"                      alt="YouTube Music app on the Pixel 7"                > </p><p>Hannah Stryker &#x2F; How-To Geek</p><p> As you know, “liking” a song by tapping the thumbs-up button tells YouTube Music that you enjoy the song, style, artist, and other factors. That one action could greatly impact the songs, videos, or podcasts it’ll serve up in the future. Naturally, the same applies to disliking a song or artist by hitting the thumbs-down button on YouTube Music.</p><p> When you first signed up for YouTube Music, you probably constantly hit those little thumbs up&#x2F;down buttons to help the system learn. However, many of us get out of the habit, not to mention letting songs play randomly while driving.</p><p> So, try to stay vigilant. Instead of hitting “next” to skip a song or artist you don’t enjoy, make sure you tell Uncle YouTube and give it a thumbs-down. It’s also worth mentioning that recommendations are “based on the artists that you subscribe to on YouTube Music <em>and</em> YouTube,” so consider that when watching music videos inside the YouTube app.</p><h2 id="Try-the-Music-Tuner-to-Create-a-Radio"><a href="#Try-the-Music-Tuner-to-Create-a-Radio" class="headerlink" title="Try the Music Tuner to Create a Radio"></a>Try the Music Tuner to Create a Radio</h2><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static1.howtogeekimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/your-music-tuner-option-in-youtube-music.jpg"                      alt="Your music tuner option in YouTube Music."                > </p><p> Initially, YouTube Music didn’t have many features compared to the competition. Thankfully, the team has continuously added new goodies, a <a class="link"   href="https://win-solutions.techidaily.com/msi-afterburner-doesnt-see-your-gpu-in-windows-n-solutions-unveiled/" >comment section <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>, and more over the years. Perhaps the best feature, in my opinion, is the “Your Music Tuner” on the app’s home page.</p><p> You can create your own radio station on YouTube Music, serving the best songs tailored to your tastes. Oddly enough, it’s never in one location, but I usually find it after scrolling down once or twice on the main home column of the YouTube Music app. So, scroll down, look for the music tuner, then create your radio station.</p><p> We’ve seen a similar radio feature on other services, like Spotify, which removed it a few years back. Thankfully, it’s still available on YouTube Music, and I’d consider it the best part of the streaming service. Creating a “Music Tuner” radio station is similar to adding artists to the recommendation list, but you’re not limited to five. Feel free to choose more, but I wouldn’t go overboard with the picks, so it has a good baseline.</p><p> Now, the algorithm does a wonderful job streaming an excellent radio station of all my favorite music.</p><h2 id="Remove-Content-You-Don’t-Enjoy"><a href="#Remove-Content-You-Don’t-Enjoy" class="headerlink" title="Remove Content You Don’t Enjoy"></a>Remove Content You Don’t Enjoy</h2><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static1.howtogeekimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/youtube-music-remove.jpg"                      alt="Removing song from YouTube Music library."                > </p><p> While liking or disliking songs will help train the algorithm, unliking a song will not automatically remove it from your Library, playlist, or recommendations machine. So, if you accidentally like something or your musical tastes have changed, you must manually remove it.</p><p> Inside the YouTube Music app, head to your Library (on the bottom right) and scroll through some of the lists of liked music and playlists. If you find any songs or artists you no longer enjoy, long-press on the song and select “Remove from Library” and&#x2F;or “Remove from Playlists.”</p><h2 id="Reset-the-YouTube-Music-Algorithm"><a href="#Reset-the-YouTube-Music-Algorithm" class="headerlink" title="Reset the YouTube Music Algorithm"></a>Reset the YouTube Music Algorithm</h2><p> Unfortunately for some, all the tips above can’t save you from whatever music your significant other (or kids) play on your account. If your music recommendations are out of control, you can clear the history and somewhat reset the YouTube Music algorithm.</p><p> To do this, <a class="link"   href="https://music.youtube.com/" >open YouTube Music on a web browser <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> and navigate to the same Settings &gt; Privacy section as earlier. Now, click “Clear Watch History” and confirm you want to proceed by clicking “Clear Watch History” again on the popup screen.</p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static1.howtogeekimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/youtube-music-video-history.jpg"                      alt="Clearing your YouTube Video and Music history."                > </p><p> Doing so will completely erase your YouTube watch history from all YouTube apps on all devices. Google says video recommendations will be reset and may influence activity on other products, including YouTube Music.</p><p> You can also clear your search history, which may affect the content suggestions across YouTube and YouTube Music. Remember that these are drastic moves and will significantly alter what you see on both apps.</p><p> Being able to go into recommendations and add artists I’m interested in did the trick for me. That, combined with being diligent in liking or disliking songs, YouTube Music continues to deliver great content, fun acoustic versions, and more, which is why it’s my preferred music streaming service.</p><p> I also <a class="link"   href="https://hardware-help.techidaily.com/enhance-performance-with-a-hid-compliant-mouse-driver-update/" >use and love YouTube Premium <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>, which makes YouTube Music ad-free and removes video ads from YouTube.</p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-format="autorelaxed"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="1223367746"></ins></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="8358498916"     data-ad-format="auto"     data-full-width-responsive="true"></ins></p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;Transforming-YouTube’s-Audio-Offerings-Essential-Strategies-for-Enhanced-Song-Recommendations&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#Transforming-YouTube’s-Audi</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="tech" scheme="https://media-tips.techidaily.com/categories/tech/"/>
    
    
    <category term="streaming" scheme="https://media-tips.techidaily.com/tags/streaming/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Step-by-Step Tutorial: Unveiling Solutions for the Persistent Black Screen When Watching YouTube on Your Android Phone or Tablet</title>
    <link href="https://media-tips.techidaily.com/step-by-step-tutorial-unveiling-solutions-for-the-persistent-black-screen-when-watching-youtube-on-your-android-phone-or-tablet/"/>
    <id>https://media-tips.techidaily.com/step-by-step-tutorial-unveiling-solutions-for-the-persistent-black-screen-when-watching-youtube-on-your-android-phone-or-tablet/</id>
    <published>2024-08-28T14:45:29.000Z</published>
    <updated>2024-08-29T03:12:14.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="Step-by-Step-Tutorial-Unveiling-Solutions-for-the-Persistent-Black-Screen-When-Watching-YouTube-on-Your-Android-Phone-or-Tablet"><a href="#Step-by-Step-Tutorial-Unveiling-Solutions-for-the-Persistent-Black-Screen-When-Watching-YouTube-on-Your-Android-Phone-or-Tablet" class="headerlink" title="Step-by-Step Tutorial: Unveiling Solutions for the Persistent Black Screen When Watching YouTube on Your Android Phone or Tablet"></a>Step-by-Step Tutorial: Unveiling Solutions for the Persistent Black Screen When Watching YouTube on Your Android Phone or Tablet</h2><h3 id="Key-Takeaways"><a href="#Key-Takeaways" class="headerlink" title="Key Takeaways"></a>Key Takeaways</h3><ul><li>To fix a black screen issue in YouTube on Android, head into Settings &gt; Apps &gt; YouTube &gt; Storage and tap “Clear Cache.” If that doesn’t work, go back one screen, choose “Force Stop,” and then “OK.”</li><li>Another method is to disable and re-enable the app. Go to Settings &gt; Apps &gt; YouTube and select “Disable” followed by “Disable App.” Wait for ten seconds and tap “Enable.”</li><li>The last solution is to restart your Android phone. Pull down twice from the top of the phone’s screen, tap the Power icon, and choose “Restart.”</li></ul><p> If the YouTube app on your Android phone displays a black screen instead of the actual content, it’s likely the app’s cache is corrupted. There are other reasons this issue occurs, and we’ll show you how to fix it using various ways on your phone.</p><h2 id="Clear-YouTube’s-App-Cache"><a href="#Clear-YouTube’s-App-Cache" class="headerlink" title="Clear YouTube’s App Cache"></a>Clear YouTube’s App Cache</h2><p> YouTube caches various files to preload certain elements in the app. This makes your app experience faster. However, if these cache files become corrupted, you may experience issues in the app. This might be the case if the Android app is displaying a black screen instead of playing the video.</p><p> In this case, <a class="link"   href="https://digital-screen-recording.techidaily.com/new-inexpensive-pc-monitoring-software-for-2024/" >remove the app’s cache files <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> to fix the problem. Doing so doesn’t delete your data in the app, and the app will rebuild the cache. To do that, on your Android phone, navigate to Settings &gt; Apps &gt; YouTube &gt; Storage. At the bottom of the page, tap “Clear Cache.”</p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static1.howtogeekimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/1-remove-youtube-cache-android.jpg"                      alt="&#39;Clear Cache&#39; highlighted for YouTube in Android Settings."                > </p><p> When the cache is cleared, you’ll see “Cache” occupying 0 (zero) storage space.</p><h2 id="Force-Stop-and-Relaunch-YouTube"><a href="#Force-Stop-and-Relaunch-YouTube" class="headerlink" title="Force Stop and Relaunch YouTube"></a>Force Stop and Relaunch YouTube</h2><p> Another reason you’ve encountered the black screen issue on YouTube could be any number of minor glitches. A simple force close and <a class="link"   href="https://tech-savvy.techidaily.com/optimizing-productivity-4-strategies-with-chatgpt/" >relaunch of the app <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> can often fix those items.</p><p> On your phone, navigate to Settings &gt; Apps &gt; YouTube. In the bottom-right corner, tap “Force Stop.”</p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static1.howtogeekimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/2-force-stop-youtube-android.jpg"                      alt="&#39;Force Stop&#39; highlighted for YouTube in Android Settings."                > </p><p> In the prompt that opens, select “OK.”</p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static1.howtogeekimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/3-force-stop-prompt.jpg"                      alt="&#39;OK&#39; highlighted in the &#39;Force Stop&#39; prompt."                > </p><p> Close Settings. Open the phone’s app drawer, find YouTube, and tap the app to relaunch it. Feel free to relaunch the app from the home screen if you wish.</p><h2 id="Uninstall-the-App"><a href="#Uninstall-the-App" class="headerlink" title="Uninstall the App"></a>Uninstall the App</h2><p> Since YouTube is a stock Google app, most Android phones don’t allow you to <a class="link"   href="https://howto.techidaily.com/9-solutions-to-fix-honor-x50-gt-system-crash-issue-drfone-by-drfone-fix-android-problems-fix-android-problems/" >remove it completely <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>. If yours does, navigate to Settings &gt; Apps &gt; YouTube and choose “Uninstall.” Then, reinstall <a class="link"   href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/links/3607085/type/dlg/sid/UUhtgUeUpU2001677/https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.google.android.youtube" >YouTube from the Google Play Store <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>.</p><p> If you don’t find the “Uninstall” option (which is the case with most phones), disable and re-enable the app. This helps fix some app problems. To do that, head into Settings &gt; Apps &gt; YouTube. From the bottom bar, select “Disable.”</p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static1.howtogeekimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/4-disable-youtube-android.jpg"                      alt="&#39;Disable&#39; highlighted for YouTube in Android Settings."                > </p><p> In the open prompt, select “Disable App.” This removes the app from your phone’s app drawer and home screen, making it feel like you’ve uninstalled it. (The app still exists on the phone.)</p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static1.howtogeekimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/5-disable-app-prompt.jpg"                      alt="&#39;Disable App&#39; highlighted in the prompt."                > </p><p> Wait for about ten seconds. Then, from the same bottom bar, select “Enable” to re-enable the app.</p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static1.howtogeekimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/6-enable-youtube-android.jpg"                      alt="&#39;Enable&#39; highlighted for YouTube in Android Settings."                > </p><h2 id="Restart-Your-Phone"><a href="#Restart-Your-Phone" class="headerlink" title="Restart Your Phone"></a>Restart Your Phone</h2><p> Your phone’s minor glitches can cause YouTube not to function as expected. In this case, <a class="link"   href="https://location-fake.techidaily.com/3utools-virtual-location-not-working-on-apple-iphone-8-fix-now-drfone-by-drfone-virtual-ios/" >give your Android phone a reboot <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> to resolve various system problems. How you turn off and back on your phone depends on the model.</p><p> On most Android phones, you’ll press and hold down the Power button and select “Restart” in the open menu to reboot the phone. If pressing that key opens the voice assistant, use the Volume Down + Power key combination. Note that this combination force-reboots some phones.</p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static1.howtogeekimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/7-restart-android-phone.jpg"                      alt="&#39;Restart&#39; highlighted in Android&#39;s Power menu."                > </p><p> If your phone still won’t reboot, use a Quick Settings option to turn off and back on your phone. Do that by pulling down twice from the top of your phone’s screen, tapping the Power icon, and choosing “Restart.” When the phone turns back on, launch YouTube, and it should work as expected. Enjoy!</p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-format="autorelaxed"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="1223367746"></ins></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="8358498916"     data-ad-format="auto"     data-full-width-responsive="true"></ins></p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;Step-by-Step-Tutorial-Unveiling-Solutions-for-the-Persistent-Black-Screen-When-Watching-YouTube-on-Your-Android-Phone-or-Tablet&quot;&gt;&lt;a </summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="tech" scheme="https://media-tips.techidaily.com/categories/tech/"/>
    
    
    <category term="streaming" scheme="https://media-tips.techidaily.com/tags/streaming/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Revamped Spotify TV Application Now Streamlines Your Viewing Experience</title>
    <link href="https://media-tips.techidaily.com/revamped-spotify-tv-application-now-streamlines-your-viewing-experience/"/>
    <id>https://media-tips.techidaily.com/revamped-spotify-tv-application-now-streamlines-your-viewing-experience/</id>
    <published>2024-08-28T14:42:49.000Z</published>
    <updated>2024-08-29T04:30:44.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="Revamped-Spotify-TV-Application-Now-Streamlines-Your-Viewing-Experience"><a href="#Revamped-Spotify-TV-Application-Now-Streamlines-Your-Viewing-Experience" class="headerlink" title="Revamped Spotify TV Application Now Streamlines Your Viewing Experience"></a>Revamped Spotify TV Application Now Streamlines Your Viewing Experience</h2><p>After years of neglect, the Spotify TV app is getting a much-needed overhaul. The app now features a <a class="link"   href="https://newsroom.spotify.com/2023-11-09/find-your-favorite-audio-more-easily-with-the-redesigned-spotify-on-tv-experience/" >redesigned interface <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> that’s more intuitive, easier to use, and visually appealing. It’s a far cry from the Spotify TV app that we’ve tolerated for so many years, and it should feel familiar to everyone who uses Spotify on desktop or mobile.</p><p> The new Spotify TV home page is basically a widescreen version of the mobile app. Recently played content appears at the top of the home page, and if you scroll down, you’re greeted by a plethora of personalized recommendations. Search and Library tabs are still located at the top of the home screen, but they’re joined by a mini player that shows your current song or podcast.</p><p> More importantly, the Spotify TV app has abandoned its old “Now Playing” queue system. The old queue system highlighted album art at the expense of useability—you could only see <em>one</em> upcoming track. Spotify’s new queue system is much more useful, as it lists several upcoming tracks in a vertical column on your TV. Album art is still included for each track, but in a more modest fashion. You can also enable dark mode to tone down Spotify’s more flashy elements.</p><p> And if your friends or family have bad taste, you’ll appreciate the Spotify TV app’s updated account-switching feature. A user profile icon now appears at the top-right corner of the Spotify TV app. Clicking this icon allows you to switch to a different account. It’s very similar to the profile system on Netflix or Hulu.</p><p> These changes make the Spotify TV app more useful and usable. Still, navigating Spotify with a TV remote isn’t a very fun experience. If you want to make things easier for yourself, use <a class="link"   href="https://support.spotify.com/us/article/spotify-connect/" >Spotify Connect <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> to cast content from your phone to your TV. You can do that by opening Spotify on your phone and start playing a song, then tap the device icon next to the pause button at the bottom of your screen. Then, select your TV from the list of available devices.</p><p> The redesigned Spotify app is currently rolling out to smart TVs, streaming sticks, and game consoles. A premium membership is not required.</p><p> Source: <a class="link"   href="https://newsroom.spotify.com/2023-11-09/find-your-favorite-audio-more-easily-with-the-redesigned-spotify-on-tv-experience/" >Spotify <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> via <a class="link"   href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/11/9/23953719/spotify-tv-app-redesign-update" >The Verge <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-format="autorelaxed"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="1223367746"></ins></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="8358498916"     data-ad-format="auto"     data-full-width-responsive="true"></ins></p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;Revamped-Spotify-TV-Application-Now-Streamlines-Your-Viewing-Experience&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#Revamped-Spotify-TV-Application-Now-Streamlines-Y</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="tech" scheme="https://media-tips.techidaily.com/categories/tech/"/>
    
    
    <category term="streaming" scheme="https://media-tips.techidaily.com/tags/streaming/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Exploring the World of Ultra HD: The Ins and Outs of 4K Resolution Technology</title>
    <link href="https://media-tips.techidaily.com/exploring-the-world-of-ultra-hd-the-ins-and-outs-of-4k-resolution-technology/"/>
    <id>https://media-tips.techidaily.com/exploring-the-world-of-ultra-hd-the-ins-and-outs-of-4k-resolution-technology/</id>
    <published>2024-08-28T14:33:14.000Z</published>
    <updated>2024-08-29T02:52:30.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="Exploring-the-World-of-Ultra-HD-The-Ins-and-Outs-of-4K-Resolution-Technology"><a href="#Exploring-the-World-of-Ultra-HD-The-Ins-and-Outs-of-4K-Resolution-Technology" class="headerlink" title="Exploring the World of Ultra HD: The Ins and Outs of 4K Resolution Technology"></a>Exploring the World of Ultra HD: The Ins and Outs of 4K Resolution Technology</h2><h3 id="Quick-Links"><a href="#Quick-Links" class="headerlink" title="Quick Links"></a>Quick Links</h3><ul><li><a class="link"   href="https://tech-revival.techidaily.com/what-chatgpt-accessing-up-to-date-information-means-for-everyone/" >It’s All About Resolution <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></li><li><a class="link"   href="https://fox-boxes.techidaily.com/2024-approved-top-professional-camera-choices-complete-360-guide-2023/" >4K and UHD Are Different <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></li><li><a class="link"   href="https://win11-tips.techidaily.com/how-to-eradicate-system-call-issues-on-modern-windows/" >What About 1440p? <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></li><li><a class="link"   href="https://youtube-web.techidaily.com/forming-frost-into-warmth-video-backdrops-guide/" >Things to Consider When Upgrading to 4K <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></li><li><a class="link"   href="https://some-knowledge.techidaily.com/updated-fading-out-sound-fl-studio-guide/" >Upscaling to Ultra HD <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></li><li><a class="link"   href="https://hardware-help.techidaily.com/top-rated-bluetooth-keyboards-of-2024-a-buyers-guide/" >What About HDR? <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></li><li><a class="link"   href="https://android-frp.techidaily.com/in-2024-the-complete-guide-to-poco-frp-bypass-everything-you-need-to-know-by-drfone-android/" >Don’t Worry About the Terminology <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></li></ul><h3 id="Key-Takeaways"><a href="#Key-Takeaways" class="headerlink" title="Key Takeaways"></a>Key Takeaways</h3><ul><li>4K &amp; UHD refer to a resolution four times that of 1080p, providing cleaner, more detailed images.</li><li>4K is a production standard, UHD is a display resolution, and both are used interchangeably.</li><li>Consider your viewing distance, 4K content availability, internet speed, and device compatibility before upgrading.</li></ul><p> The vast majority of new TVs are marketed as 4K displays, also known as Ultra HD. So what makes 4K different from standard HD, and what do you need to know about upgrading?</p><h2 id="It’s-All-About-Resolution"><a href="#It’s-All-About-Resolution" class="headerlink" title="It’s All About Resolution"></a>It’s All About Resolution</h2><p> Commonly, 4K and UHD refer to a resolution that’s a step up from 1080p (or “full HD”). A 4K UHD display has roughly four times the pixels of the previous generation, which creates a cleaner, more detailed image.</p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static1.howtogeekimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/52759736211_7dc316918e_o.jpg"                      alt="Blade Runner and Detective Pikachu on Blu-ray disc."                > </p><p>Corbin Davenport &#x2F; How-To Geek</p><p> A 1080p high-definition TV isn’t able to take full advantage of 4K media since there aren’t enough pixels available. At the same time, to get the full benefit of a 4K display the media you are watching will also need to be in 4K resolution.</p><p> Fortunately, 4K or Ultra HD is everywhere, from movies and TV shows to the latest video games. You can also buy a <a class="link"   href="https://screen-recording.techidaily.com/updated-instant-display-image-any-window-os-for-2024/" >UHD 4K monitor for your computer <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> for lots of screen real estate and excellent image quality. Your smartphone probably shoots video in 4K (some even manage 8K), even if the massive video files aren’t worth it on a smaller display.</p><h2 id="4K-and-UHD-Are-Different"><a href="#4K-and-UHD-Are-Different" class="headerlink" title="4K and UHD Are Different"></a>4K and UHD Are Different</h2><p> Despite being used interchangeably by manufacturers, retailers, and consumers alike, 4K and Ultra HD (UHD) are technically different. While 4K is a production standard as defined by the Digital Cinema Initiatives (DCI), UHD is just a display resolution. Films are produced in DCI 4K, while most TVs have a resolution that matches UHD.</p><p> The 4K production standard specifies a resolution of 4096 x 2160 pixels, twice the width and length of the previous standard of 2048 x 1080, or 2K. As part of this production standard, 4K also specifies the type of compression that should be used (JPEG2000), the maximum bitrate (up to 250 Mbits per second), and color depth specifications (12-bit, 4:4:4).</p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static1.howtogeekimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/4k_compared_edited.png"                      alt="4K resolution compared to Ultra HD, 1080p, 720p, and more."                > </p><p> Ultra HD has a display resolution of 3840 x 2160 pixels, and it’s used in the vast majority of modern TVs, even those advertised with an eye-catching “4K” label. Besides the number of on-screen pixels, there aren’t any additional specifications. The real differences between the two formats are the width of the images and the aspect ratios.</p><p> A movie produced in 4K can use an aspect ratio of up to 1.9:1, although, most filmmakers prefer 1.85:1 or 2.39:1. Video games rendered for consumer-level displays typically use the UHD aspect ratio of 1.78:1 to fill the screen.</p><p> This is why you’ll continue to see letterboxing (black bars at the top and bottom of the screen) when you watch movies on your brand-new UHD television. Because UHD doesn’t specify any additional standards, older televisions with 8-bit panels are advertised as UHD sets alongside new, 10-bit (and the future 12-bit) UHD displays.</p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static1.howtogeekimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/8k_compared_edited.png"                      alt="8K resolution compared to 4K, Full HD, and SD."                > </p><p> To make matters worse, Ultra HD is also used for so-called 8K content. Labeled as “8K UHD” (as opposed to 4K UHD), this refers to content with a resolution of 7680 x 4320 pixels. This leap in quality is enormous in terms of overall pixel count, but the benefits to most are limited. It will be a while before we see widespread content produced for this format.</p><p> Many manufacturers use the term “2160p” to describe regular UHD content, even though it isn’t strictly accurate about production standards.</p><h2 id="What-About-1440p"><a href="#What-About-1440p" class="headerlink" title="What About 1440p?"></a>What About 1440p?</h2><p> 1440p sits between “Full HD” (1080p) and 4K or Ultra HD (2160p), in reference to the resolution 2560 x 1440p. This resolution doesn’t apply to TVs, but rather PC monitors especially those aimed at gamers. 1440p has become a sweet spot in PC gaming where resolution is appreciably improved over 1080p, while still allowing mid-range machines to be performant in terms of frame rate.</p><p> Some refer to 1440p as <a class="link"   href="https://eaxpv-info.techidaily.com/new-2024-approved-how-to-binge-worthy-music-reaction-videos-on-youtube/" >Quad HD or QHD <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>. Others use the term “2K” even though this isn’t strictly accurate. It can also apply to a range of resolutions with a vertical resolution of 1440 pixels, including <a class="link"   href="https://location-social.techidaily.com/does-find-my-friends-work-on-realme-c55-drfone-by-drfone-virtual-android/" >ultrawide and super ultrawide monitors <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>.</p><h2 id="Things-to-Consider-When-Upgrading-to-4K"><a href="#Things-to-Consider-When-Upgrading-to-4K" class="headerlink" title="Things to Consider When Upgrading to 4K"></a>Things to Consider When Upgrading to 4K</h2><p> It’s a great time to upgrade to a UHD TV capable of 4K playback, as technology has matured considerably over the last five years. Not only are UHD displays now much cheaper, but they also come with more features. There are 10-bit panels capable of displaying high-dynamic-range content that also have powerful onboard image processors.</p><p> For the leap to be worth it, you’ll need to consider how large you want your display to be and how far away you sit from it. According to <a class="link"   href="https://www.rtings.com/tv/reviews/by-size/size-to-distance-relationship" >RTINGS <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>, the upgrade isn’t worth it if you sit farther than six feet away from a 50-inch screen. You can’t see the pixels from that distance, anyway, so you won’t benefit from the increased resolution.</p><p> Another thing worth considering is what 4K content you’ll be watching on a new TV. Ultra-HD Blu-rays provide <a class="link"   href="https://android-pokemon-go.techidaily.com/in-2024-the-most-useful-tips-for-pokemon-go-ultra-league-on-oppo-a78-drfone-by-drfone-virtual-android/" >the best at-home viewing experience <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>, and there’s a sizable catalog that’s growing all of the time. If you don’t often buy expensive discs, though, you might be stuck streaming content, instead.</p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static1.howtogeekimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/dark_city_bluray.jpg"                      alt="Dark City on Blu-ray."                > </p><p>Tim Brookes &#x2F; How-To Geek</p><p> This is where the speed of your internet connection can make or break your investment in a shiny new TV. Netflix claims its customers need an internet speed of 25 Mbits per second or better to stream Ultra HD. You can <a class="link"   href="https://screen-mirror.techidaily.com/how-to-cast-vivo-s17e-screen-to-pc-using-wifi-drfone-by-drfone-android/" >test your internet speed <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> to find out how your display will fare. Remember, though, these speeds can dip considerably during busy periods (like when everyone’s streaming Netflix simultaneously).</p><p> You’ll also have to pay for a premium-level streaming subscription to access the highest-quality content. Netflix gates its UHD content behind a $22.99 monthly fee. This includes Netflix Originals, and many other movies and series not produced by the streaming giant. Unfortunately, a lot of movies that have UHD releases are still presented in HD on Netflix.</p><p> Do you have older HD devices, like a Roku or Apple TV? These can pose an issue, as they’re only capable of delivering a 1080p image. You’ll need a Chromecast Ultra or Apple TV 4K if you want to take advantage of higher resolution and HDR playback. This is less of an issue for your TV, as long as it has a stable and responsive OS, which many do.</p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static1.howtogeekimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/2-11.png"                      alt="Apple TV device on a black background."                > </p><p><a class="link"   href="https://www.shutterstock.com/image-photo/berlin-germany-august-21-2016-product-471991831" >Lebedev Yury&#x2F;Shutterstock.com <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><p> Remember that 4K shines on larger displays. Unfortunately, when you upgrade to a larger native UHD TV, any 1080p content will look worse. This will be less of a problem in the future, though, and there are some solutions.</p><h2 id="Upscaling-to-Ultra-HD"><a href="#Upscaling-to-Ultra-HD" class="headerlink" title="Upscaling to Ultra HD"></a>Upscaling to Ultra HD</h2><p> TVs place a heavy emphasis on <a class="link"   href="https://extra-information.techidaily.com/your-roadmap-to-mastery-the-ultimate-guide-to-google-podcasting/" >upscaling <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>, which takes lower resolution content and scales it to fit a much larger display. Remember, there are four times as many pixels on an Ultra HD display than there are on a regular Full HD television.</p><p> Upscaling means more than simply stretching an image. Modern TVs and playback devices process the image and attempt to reconstruct it to look its best at a higher resolution. This is done via a process known as interpolation, during which missing pixels are generated on the fly. The intent is to produce a smooth transition between contrasting areas of the image.</p><p> As TVs become more powerful, better interpolation and upscaling techniques will be used. The <a class="link"   href="https://www.nvidia.com/en-us/shield/" >NVIDIA Shield <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>has some of the best upscaling technology on the market. It utilizes AI and machine learning to improve different parts of the image using different techniques.</p><p> If you upgraded to an Ultra HD TV and have noticed subpar performance with lower-resolution content, a Shield might be just what you need.</p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static1.howtogeekimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/02/52749705515_41f21b4f0c_o.jpg"                      alt="Xbox Series X console in an entertainment unit."                > </p><p>Hannah Stryker &#x2F; How-To Geek</p><p> Xbox Series X and PlayStation 5 game consoles output at a native 4K resolution, though a native 4K image is rare. Games instead rely on <a class="link"   href="https://facebook-videos.techidaily.com/2024-approved-instagram-story-width-height-run-time/" >dynamic resolution scaling <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> to adjust the output resolution on the fly in order to hit performance targets. These games still look great on a 4K TV, just make sure you opt for one with a <a class="link"   href="https://change-location.techidaily.com/how-to-use-snapchat-location-spoofer-to-protect-your-privacy-on-vivo-y100i-power-5g-drfone-by-drfone-virtual-android/" >120Hz refresh rate <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> and <a class="link"   href="https://some-knowledge.techidaily.com/updated-full-length-video-view-remove-youtube-preview/" >plenty of HDMI 2.1 ports <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>.</p><p> NVIDIA has developed Deep Learning Super Sampling to render games at lower resolutions and upscale them in real-time to 4K and better. AMD and Intel now have similar technologies. These allow you to put your 4K display to good use while still hitting your desired frame rate by limiting how many raw pixels the GPU renders.</p><h2 id="What-About-HDR"><a href="#What-About-HDR" class="headerlink" title="What About HDR?"></a>What About HDR?</h2><p><a class="link"   href="https://win-able.techidaily.com/defeating-pc-launch-obstacles-in-days-gone-a-step-by-step-troubleshooting-guide/" >High dynamic range (HDR) <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> is also often advertised on movies and TVs, and it’s an entirely different technology. While 4K is a production standard and UHD is a resolution, HDR is a loosely defined term that refers to a wider color gamut and higher peak brightness. It’s the other big benefit of upgrading your old TV. </p><p> Brighter images deliver a more immersive viewing experience. HDR allows the image to really pop since it more closely imitates the difference between light and dark that we see in the “real world.” Most TVs will support basic HDR10, while others support technologies that can deliver a more dynamic image like <a class="link"   href="https://extra-hints.techidaily.com/best-drone-buddies-kids-most-enjoyed-toy-companions-for-2024/" >Dolby Vision <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> and <a class="link"   href="https://some-guidance.techidaily.com/new-the-pathway-to-prosperity-a-graphic-designers-journey/" >HDR10+ <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>.</p><p> Modern game consoles like the Xbox Series X and PlayStation 5 both support some form of HDR, which can make just as much of an impact on the image as the jump in resolution from HD to Ultra HD. Xbox and Windows even support Auto-HDR which <a class="link"   href="https://extra-information.techidaily.com/new-apple-music-and-video-harmony-explained/" >intelligently applies HDR to older games <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> that do not explicitly support it.</p><p> While 1080p HDR can exist, HDR content wasn’t widely produced during the “Full HD” age, so you won’t find any televisions on the market that offer HDR at 1080p. The vast majority of 4K sets on the market do support HDR in some form, however. </p><h2 id="Don’t-Worry-About-the-Terminology"><a href="#Don’t-Worry-About-the-Terminology" class="headerlink" title="Don’t Worry About the Terminology"></a>Don’t Worry About the Terminology</h2><p> Whether it’s called 4K or UHD doesn’t matter. Your UHD TV is 4K-capable. The world has just adjusted to the nebulous terms thrown around by manufacturers and marketers.</p><p> Netflix might advertise a movie in Ultra HD, while Apple labels the same movie as 4K. Your TV doesn’t care and will play both just fine.</p><p> Before you head out to buy that new set, though, be sure to check out <a class="link"   href="https://buynow-tips.techidaily.com/from-legendary-to-iconic-how-improved-graphics-elevate-the-great-demons-souls-game/" >these common mistakes people make when shopping for a TV <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>.</p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-format="autorelaxed"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="1223367746"></ins></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="8358498916"     data-ad-format="auto"     data-full-width-responsive="true"></ins></p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;Exploring-the-World-of-Ultra-HD-The-Ins-and-Outs-of-4K-Resolution-Technology&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#Exploring-the-World-of-Ultra-HD-The-Ins-and-</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="tech" scheme="https://media-tips.techidaily.com/categories/tech/"/>
    
    
    <category term="streaming" scheme="https://media-tips.techidaily.com/tags/streaming/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>1. Successful Guide: Streaming Your Favorite Twitch Channels via Roku</title>
    <link href="https://media-tips.techidaily.com/1-successful-guide-streaming-your-favorite-twitch-channels-via-roku/"/>
    <id>https://media-tips.techidaily.com/1-successful-guide-streaming-your-favorite-twitch-channels-via-roku/</id>
    <published>2024-08-28T14:32:22.000Z</published>
    <updated>2024-08-29T02:15:24.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="1-Successful-Guide-Streaming-Your-Favorite-Twitch-Channels-via-Roku"><a href="#1-Successful-Guide-Streaming-Your-Favorite-Twitch-Channels-via-Roku" class="headerlink" title="1. Successful Guide: Streaming Your Favorite Twitch Channels via Roku"></a>1. Successful Guide: Streaming Your Favorite Twitch Channels via Roku</h2><h3 id="Quick-Links"><a href="#Quick-Links" class="headerlink" title="Quick Links"></a>Quick Links</h3><ul><li><a class="link"   href="https://win-solutions.techidaily.com/resolved-how-to-overcome-minecraft-server-disconnect-problems/" >Can You Get Twitch on Roku? <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></li><li><a class="link"   href="https://snapchat-videos.techidaily.com/guide-to-flawless-transition-of-phone-cookies-from-device-to-social-media-for-2024/" >Option 1: Install an Unofficial Twitch App <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></li><li><a class="link"   href="https://tech-recovery.techidaily.com/troubleshooting-tips-for-when-you-encounter-a-missing-user32dll-file/" >Option 2: Cast Twitch to Your Roku <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></li></ul><h3 id="Key-Takeaways"><a href="#Key-Takeaways" class="headerlink" title="Key Takeaways"></a>Key Takeaways</h3><ul><li>Twitch is not available on Roku devices via an official app due to its removal in 2017.</li><li>Unofficial apps like Twoku and Stitch are options, but may not work in the future.</li><li>An alternative method is to cast Twitch from your iPhone, Mac, Windows PC, or Android device.</li></ul><p> Twitch is the premier platform for watching esports tournaments, industry events, and gaming personalities. However, Amazon (Twitch’s owner) pulled the official app from the <a class="link"   href="https://channelstore.roku.com/browse" >Roku Channel Store <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> back in 2017. There are still unofficial ways to watch Twitch on Roku TVs, though.</p><h2 id="Can-You-Get-Twitch-on-Roku"><a href="#Can-You-Get-Twitch-on-Roku" class="headerlink" title="Can You Get Twitch on Roku?"></a>Can You Get Twitch on Roku?</h2><p> You can watch Twitch on a Roku device, but not with an official app on the TV. As mentioned, Amazon pulled the Twitch app from the Roku Channel Store in 2017. For a while, there was an unofficial app that would simply install the old official Twitch app on your Roku. However, that stopped working in March 2022.</p><p> So, you’re left with two options if you’d like to watch Twitch on your Roku device. There are still a couple of unofficial apps that work, and there’s a method that utilizes the Twitch app on your smartphone.</p><h2 id="Option-1-Install-an-Unofficial-Twitch-App"><a href="#Option-1-Install-an-Unofficial-Twitch-App" class="headerlink" title="Option 1: Install an Unofficial Twitch App"></a>Option 1: Install an Unofficial Twitch App</h2><p> There are two popular alternatives to the long-gone official Twitch app: Twoku and Stitch. Note that due to changes to “unofficial” channels and with the introduction of “Beta Channels,” it’s possible these apps won’t work in the future. If you follow these instructions and they don’t work, it probably isn’t something you’re doing wrong</p><p> For Twoku, direct any web browser to the <a class="link"   href="https://my.roku.com/account/add" >Add Channel page <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>. Enter the channel code “C6ZVZD” and click “Add Channel.” Alternatively, you can <a class="link"   href="https://my.roku.com/account/add?channel=C6ZVZD" >click this link to have the code filled in automatically <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>.</p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static1.howtogeekimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/2024-03-22_16-52-23.png"                      alt="Entering channel code for Roku."                > </p><p> If the Twoku app doesn’t appear immediately in the Home menu, restart your Roku by navigating to Settings &gt; System &gt; System Restart from the Roku Home screen.</p><p> For Stitch, the process is exactly the same as outlined above. However, the code you’ll need to enter is “LL5GKQ.” You can also <a class="link"   href="https://my.roku.com/account/add?channel=LL5GKQ" >click this link to fill in the code automatically <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>.</p><h2 id="Option-2-Cast-Twitch-to-Your-Roku"><a href="#Option-2-Cast-Twitch-to-Your-Roku" class="headerlink" title="Option 2: Cast Twitch to Your Roku"></a>Option 2: Cast Twitch to Your Roku</h2><p> The most “official” method is to cast or screen mirror the official Twitch app from your iPhone, Mac, Windows PC, or Android device. The Apple devices use AirPlay, while supported Windows and Android devices can mirror their displays. The downside to screen mirroring is you can’t do something else on your device while watching Twitch.</p><p> Check our our full guides for <a class="link"   href="https://facebook-video-footage.techidaily.com/new-in-2024-autoplay-youtube-on-phones-without-interruption/" >using AirPlay with Roku <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> and <a class="link"   href="https://some-knowledge.techidaily.com/new-from-zero-to-hero-navigating-youtubes-growth-journey/" >screen mirroring to Roku devices <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>. The latter is not an ideal situation, but it does work if you’d like to bypass all the unofficial solutions completely.</p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-format="autorelaxed"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="1223367746"></ins></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="8358498916"     data-ad-format="auto"     data-full-width-responsive="true"></ins></p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;1-Successful-Guide-Streaming-Your-Favorite-Twitch-Channels-via-Roku&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#1-Successful-Guide-Streaming-Your-Favorite-Twitch-Cha</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="tech" scheme="https://media-tips.techidaily.com/categories/tech/"/>
    
    
    <category term="streaming" scheme="https://media-tips.techidaily.com/tags/streaming/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Temporary Suspension of Venu&#39;s Live Sports Streaming Explained</title>
    <link href="https://media-tips.techidaily.com/temporary-suspension-of-venus-live-sports-streaming-explained/"/>
    <id>https://media-tips.techidaily.com/temporary-suspension-of-venus-live-sports-streaming-explained/</id>
    <published>2024-08-28T14:28:44.000Z</published>
    <updated>2024-08-29T02:46:49.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="Temporary-Suspension-of-Venu’s-Live-Sports-Streaming-Explained"><a href="#Temporary-Suspension-of-Venu’s-Live-Sports-Streaming-Explained" class="headerlink" title="Temporary Suspension of Venu’s Live Sports Streaming Explained"></a>Temporary Suspension of Venu’s Live Sports Streaming Explained</h2><p>Disney, Warner Bros. Discovery, and Fox have been working on a new sports streaming service called Venu Sports. Those plans are now on hold, as a federal judge has paused the service’s launch with an injunction in favor of Fubo TV.</p><p><a class="link"   href="https://ai-driven-video-production.techidaily.com/new-2024-approved-the-great-debate-final-cut-pro-vs-lumafusion-for-video-editing/" >Venu Sports <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> was announced as a streaming service with access to many live sports channels, including ESPN, ESPN2, ABC, Fox, FS1, TNT, TBS, and others, with <a class="link"   href="https://win-answers.techidaily.com/resolved-issue-addressed-persistent-app-failures-for-wot-blitz-users/" >initial pricing <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> of $42.99 per month. Venu Sports also planned to include on-demand content from the three company’s libraries (like ESPN’s <em>30 for 30</em>). It could potentially allow many people to drop their traditional TV packages, since live sports coverage is one of the few remaining reasons to pay for TV over streaming services.</p><p> Fubo TV, a TV streaming service primarily targeted at sports streaming, launched a lawsuit immediately after Venu Sports was announced. Fubo accused the service of violating antitrust law, stating that Disney, Fox, and Warner already charge Fubo “as much as 30%-50%+ higher than rates they charge other distributors” for access to channels. The companies also force Fubo to include non-sports channels in packages intended for watching sports. A theoretical Venu Sports service wouldn’t have to pass on those extra distribution costs to customers, undercutting Fubo and other similar TV services.</p><p> United States District Judge Margaret M. Garnett granted an injunction in Fubo’s favor, preventing Venu Sports from launching, at least temporarily. The statement explains, “if the JV [the Venu Sports joint venture] is allowed to launch, it will be the only option on the market for those television consumers who want to spend their money on multiple live sports channels they love to watch, but not on superfluous entertainment channels they do not. And the JV’s corporate owners—the JV Defendants—are the same players that used their longstanding bundling practices to create the void in the pay TV market tailor-made for the live-sports-only JV to fill, and also exercise near-monopolistic control over the ability for a different live-sports-only streaming service to exist and compete with the JV.”</p><p> Fubo celebrated the injunction, saying in a press release, “Fubo’s goal is to ensure a competitive sports streaming marketplace that offers consumers choice, affordable pricing, flexibility and innovation. All distributors should have the opportunity to compete in a fair market, according to Fubo.”</p><p> This is only a temporary injunction, and Fubo’s lawsuit against Disney, Fox, and Warner is still ongoing with no confirmed court date.</p><p> Source: <a class="link"   href="https://ir.fubo.tv/news/news-details/2024/Fubo-Wins-Preliminary-Injunction-Against-The-Walt-Disney-Company-FOX-Corp.-and-Warner-Bros.-Discoverys-Venu-Sports-Joint-Venture/default.aspx" >Fubo <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>, <a class="link"   href="https://www.courtlistener.com/docket/68276963/290/fubotv-inc-v-the-walt-disney-company/" >Court Listener <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>, <a class="link"   href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/8/16/24222035/venu-sports-disney-fox-wbd-blocked-court-antitrust" >The Verge <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-format="autorelaxed"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="1223367746"></ins></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="8358498916"     data-ad-format="auto"     data-full-width-responsive="true"></ins></p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;Temporary-Suspension-of-Venu’s-Live-Sports-Streaming-Explained&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#Temporary-Suspension-of-Venu’s-Live-Sports-Streaming-Expla</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="tech" scheme="https://media-tips.techidaily.com/categories/tech/"/>
    
    
    <category term="streaming" scheme="https://media-tips.techidaily.com/tags/streaming/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Unveiling My Reasons: The Decision to Abandon Apple Podcasts Forever</title>
    <link href="https://media-tips.techidaily.com/unveiling-my-reasons-the-decision-to-abandon-apple-podcasts-forever/"/>
    <id>https://media-tips.techidaily.com/unveiling-my-reasons-the-decision-to-abandon-apple-podcasts-forever/</id>
    <published>2024-08-28T14:28:35.000Z</published>
    <updated>2024-08-29T03:38:12.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="Unveiling-My-Reasons-The-Decision-to-Abandon-Apple-Podcasts-Forever"><a href="#Unveiling-My-Reasons-The-Decision-to-Abandon-Apple-Podcasts-Forever" class="headerlink" title="Unveiling My Reasons: The Decision to Abandon Apple Podcasts Forever"></a>Unveiling My Reasons: The Decision to Abandon Apple Podcasts Forever</h2><h3 id="Quick-Links"><a href="#Quick-Links" class="headerlink" title="Quick Links"></a>Quick Links</h3><ul><li><a class="link"   href="https://location-social.techidaily.com/in-2024-how-to-activate-and-use-life360-ghost-mode-on-motorola-razr-40-ultra-drfone-by-drfone-virtual-android/" >There’s Too Much Focus on What I Might Like <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></li><li><a class="link"   href="https://hardware-updates.techidaily.com/dont-miss-out-apples-latest-16-inch-macbook-pro-with-m3-pro-now-500-cheaper-prime-day-countdown/" >I Didn’t Ask for Channels <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></li><li><a class="link"   href="https://driver-install.techidaily.com/keeping-astro-at-its-peak-install-and-update-tips-for-windows-users/" >Skipping and Bugs Seems Worse Than Other Apps <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></li><li><a class="link"   href="https://instagram-video-recordings.techidaily.com/2024-approved-the-comprehensive-guide-to-attractive-and-engaging-instagram-puzzle-feeds/" >Using Up Next is a Mess <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></li><li><a class="link"   href="https://on-screen-recording.techidaily.com/updated-2024-approved-stream-ready-strategies-for-crystal-clear-steam-recordings/" >If You Listened to Half an Episode… Good Luck <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></li></ul><p> Once upon a time, I relied on Apple Podcasts to listen to episodes almost every day. But after trying a third-party podcast player, I’m embarrassed to say I held on longer than I should have. I’m just loyal, I guess. Here’s why I finally gave it up and why you might want to do the same thing.</p><h2 id="There’s-Too-Much-Focus-on-What-I-Might-Like"><a href="#There’s-Too-Much-Focus-on-What-I-Might-Like" class="headerlink" title="There’s Too Much Focus on What I Might Like"></a>There’s Too Much Focus on What I <em>Might</em> Like</h2><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static1.howtogeekimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/apple-podcasts-you-might-like-list.jpeg"                      alt="Home screen of Apple podcasts with a you might like list"                > </p><p> When I open the <a class="link"   href="https://www.apple.com/apple-podcasts/" >Apple Podcasts <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> app, it’s clear that they want me to subscribe to more podcasts. In fact, the majority of the content on the home screen is trying to lure me to new shows instead of telling me what’s happening with the shows I have already decided to follow.</p><p> When compared to an app like <a class="link"   href="https://pocketcasts.com/" >Pocket Casts <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>, Apple Podcasts just doesn’t seem that interested in serving me the shows that I’ve asked for. Pocket Casts, meanwhile, opens up to a grid of my subscribed podcasts, and the “New Releases” filter quickly gives me the newest episodes—no scavenger hunt required.</p><p> The second tab in Apple Podcasts is a “Browse” tab that, yet again, directs me to popular podcasts and newsworthy episodes that don’t necessarily relate to what I typically listen to.</p><h2 id="I-Didn’t-Ask-for-Channels"><a href="#I-Didn’t-Ask-for-Channels" class="headerlink" title="I Didn’t Ask for Channels"></a>I Didn’t Ask for Channels</h2><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static1.howtogeekimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/apple-podcasts-channel.jpg"                      alt="Apple podcasts channels recommendations screen"                > </p><p> I like to create a custom podcast list of my own. While you can make a list with your favorites, the app likes to push what it calls “Channels.” These are curated lists based on podcast networks, and they’re really unnecessary, in my opinion, given that you can already search for a new podcast based on a creator.</p><p> While I like channels on Spotify, where I can see everything from a particular artist or label, I don’t need this type of filtering from podcasts. Networks already cross-promote their shows during episodes. And liking one show from a particular network doesn’t mean I’ll like their completely unrelated shows.</p><h2 id="Skipping-and-Bugs-Seems-Worse-Than-Other-Apps"><a href="#Skipping-and-Bugs-Seems-Worse-Than-Other-Apps" class="headerlink" title="Skipping and Bugs Seems Worse Than Other Apps"></a>Skipping and Bugs Seems Worse Than Other Apps</h2><p> After any Apple Podcasts update, sites like <a class="link"   href="https://www.reddit.com/r/iphone/comments/126lrq8/ios%5F164%5Fupdate%5Fcausing%5Fissues%5Fwith%5Fapple%5Fpodcast/" >Reddit <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> explode with complaints. I personally found that often, after an update, my episodes skipped, buffered, and had way more issues. It became pretty intolerable.</p><p> Any podcast app can experience lag if you don’t have a solid internet connection, but why did my downloaded Apple Podcast episodes still have issues? It escapes me that a tech giant couldn’t figure out a way to make sure my episodes didn’t skip back 10 seconds at random.</p><h2 id="Using-Up-Next-is-a-Mess"><a href="#Using-Up-Next-is-a-Mess" class="headerlink" title="Using Up Next is a Mess"></a>Using Up Next is a Mess</h2><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static1.howtogeekimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/apple-podcasts-up-next.jpg"                      alt="Apple podcasts up next list"                > </p><p> If there is a secret formula for how Apple chooses what to put in my “Up Next” row at the top of the home page, I never deciphered it. It’s different from the “New Episodes” section of the Library, which is where new episodes from your subscriptions show up.</p><p> My “Up Next” link went mostly unused, and yet it’s prioritized at the top of the home screen. <a class="link"   href="https://support.apple.com/guide/podcasts/use-up-next-poddfb50a470/mac" >According to Apple <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>, this feature is where I was supposed to “view and manage suggested episodes from shows that you saved, followed, or recently played.” I thought that’s what the Library is for, but alas.</p><h2 id="If-You-Listened-to-Half-an-Episode…-Good-Luck"><a href="#If-You-Listened-to-Half-an-Episode…-Good-Luck" class="headerlink" title="If You Listened to Half an Episode… Good Luck"></a>If You Listened to Half an Episode… Good Luck</h2><p> In my Pocket Casts app, there is a filter for in-progress episodes. If I listen to half of a history podcast episode about the British monarchy and then decide to switch to a True Crime episode, making my way back to the first show is easy. On Apple Podcasts, not so much.</p><p> There’s no streamlined way to get back to content, and that was my dealbreaker. I just needed a way to listen to the podcasts I like, not be hit with dozens of ads for other shows, and a limit to basic features.</p><hr><p> If you’re stuck on using native apps, Apple Podcasts will do. But there’s literally no reason not to download another, better, equally free app. Fewer glitches and more features are awaiting. Apple Podcasts is fine for casual listening, but if you’re serious about podcasts, <a class="link"   href="https://tech-renaissance.techidaily.com/improving-zoom-experience-when-to-blame-tech-vs-connectivity/" >you should really try a dedicated app <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>.</p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-format="autorelaxed"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="1223367746"></ins></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="8358498916"     data-ad-format="auto"     data-full-width-responsive="true"></ins></p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;Unveiling-My-Reasons-The-Decision-to-Abandon-Apple-Podcasts-Forever&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#Unveiling-My-Reasons-The-Decision-to-Abandon-Apple-Po</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="tech" scheme="https://media-tips.techidaily.com/categories/tech/"/>
    
    
    <category term="streaming" scheme="https://media-tips.techidaily.com/tags/streaming/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Revolutionizing In-Car Entertainment: The Future Without Spotify&#39;s &#39;Car Thing&#39;</title>
    <link href="https://media-tips.techidaily.com/revolutionizing-in-car-entertainment-the-future-without-spotifys-car-thing/"/>
    <id>https://media-tips.techidaily.com/revolutionizing-in-car-entertainment-the-future-without-spotifys-car-thing/</id>
    <published>2024-08-28T14:12:10.000Z</published>
    <updated>2024-08-29T04:18:56.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="Revolutionizing-In-Car-Entertainment-The-Future-Without-Spotify’s-‘Car-Thing’"><a href="#Revolutionizing-In-Car-Entertainment-The-Future-Without-Spotify’s-‘Car-Thing’" class="headerlink" title="Revolutionizing In-Car Entertainment: The Future Without Spotify’s ‘Car Thing’"></a>Revolutionizing In-Car Entertainment: The Future Without Spotify’s ‘Car Thing’</h2><p>Spotify released Car Thing back in 2022 as a dedicated Spotify media player for cars, complete with a physical knob and and voice controls. Unfortunately, all Car Thing players are about to turn into bricks.</p><p> Spotify is notifying Car Thing owners that the device will soon be discontinued, and it will stop working entirely after December 9th, 2024. Spotify recommends resetting the device to factory settings and then “safely disposing of your device following local electronic waste guidelines.” There is no trade-in program available for Spotify to properly dispose of the device for you.</p><p> Spotify initially made Car Thing available to select Spotify users, before expanding its availability to anyone with a Spotify Premium account in the United States <a class="link"   href="https://some-skills.techidaily.com/understanding-the-quantum-leap-hdr-innovations-for-2024/" >in early 2022 <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>. It was a device that could be attached to a car dashboard, with its own touch screen interface for selecting playlists, searching for music, and controlling playback. However, it still relied on a connected smartphone for its data connection, so it wasn’t all that useful if you already had Android Auto or Apple CarPlay.</p><p> Car Thing didn’t last long, as Spotify <a class="link"   href="https://some-guidance.techidaily.com/2024-approved-personalize-and-edit-iphone-ringtones-easily/" >confirmed a few months later <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> that it had stopped manufacturing due to “several factors, including product demand and supply chain issues.” The player was sold for a while longer at a fire sale price of $50, a discount of $40 from the original price (on top of the cost of the required Spotify Premium membership).</p><p> Unfortunately, Spotify also still doesn’t have plans to sell a new Car Thing or any similar devices. A support page explains, “As of now, there are no plans to release a replacement or new version of Car Thing.”</p><p> It’s not great that Spotify is turning all Car Thing players into bricks, especially after <a class="link"   href="https://newsroom.spotify.com/2022-04-07/spotifys-car-thing-device-debuts-new-features/" >software updates <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> allowed it to control other media sources and answer calls from the connected phone. It probably wouldn’t be too difficult for Spotify to keep those features functional while dropping support for the Spotify-specific features, but the company isn’t willing to do that.</p><p> The mobile Spotify app still has a Car Mode that makes buttons and other interface elements larger, so that feature combined with <a class="link"   href="https://extra-hints.techidaily.com/faster-film-fun-time-lapse-techniques-for-iphones/" >a phone mount <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> can be a partial replacement for Car Thing. If your car has Apple CarPlay or Android Auto, you can also just use that.</p><p> Source: <a class="link"   href="https://support.spotify.com/us/article/car-thing-discontinued/" >Spotify <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-format="autorelaxed"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="1223367746"></ins></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="8358498916"     data-ad-format="auto"     data-full-width-responsive="true"></ins></p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;Revolutionizing-In-Car-Entertainment-The-Future-Without-Spotify’s-‘Car-Thing’&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#Revolutionizing-In-Car-Entertainment-The-Fu</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="tech" scheme="https://media-tips.techidaily.com/categories/tech/"/>
    
    
    <category term="streaming" scheme="https://media-tips.techidaily.com/tags/streaming/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>The Smart Move: Protecting Yourself by Suspending Listening Records on Apple Music Platforms</title>
    <link href="https://media-tips.techidaily.com/the-smart-move-protecting-yourself-by-suspending-listening-records-on-apple-music-platforms/"/>
    <id>https://media-tips.techidaily.com/the-smart-move-protecting-yourself-by-suspending-listening-records-on-apple-music-platforms/</id>
    <published>2024-08-28T14:10:51.000Z</published>
    <updated>2024-08-29T04:33:29.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="The-Smart-Move-Protecting-Yourself-by-Suspending-Listening-Records-on-Apple-Music-Platforms"><a href="#The-Smart-Move-Protecting-Yourself-by-Suspending-Listening-Records-on-Apple-Music-Platforms" class="headerlink" title="The Smart Move: Protecting Yourself by Suspending Listening Records on Apple Music Platforms"></a>The Smart Move: Protecting Yourself by Suspending Listening Records on Apple Music Platforms</h2><h3 id="Key-Takeaways"><a href="#Key-Takeaways" class="headerlink" title="Key Takeaways"></a>Key Takeaways</h3><ul><li>Create a new Focus mode using the “Use Listening History” filter to keep your recommendations accurate and your history private.</li><li>Pausing your listening history can prevent unwanted tracks from influencing your music profile and recommendations.</li><li>Link your Focus mode to a specific lock screen to quickly enable or disable it, and automate it based on triggers like location or time.</li></ul><p> A new “Use Listening History” Focus filter in iOS, iPadOS, and macOS Sonoma finally lets you create private listening moments in the Music app on your iPhone, iPad, or Mac. This means that your recommendations stay accurate and your history remains private.</p><h2 id="Why-Disable-Listening-History-on-Apple-Music"><a href="#Why-Disable-Listening-History-on-Apple-Music" class="headerlink" title="Why Disable Listening History on Apple Music?"></a>Why Disable Listening History on Apple Music?</h2><p> Apple Music lacks a proper incognito toggle to prevent listening activity being recorded. Instead, you must use a Focus Mode to prevent tainting your recommendations with unwanted tracks. Apple Music’s recommendations are tailored to your listening habits and taste profile. Songs, albums, and artists you’ve listened to appear in Recently Played and on your music profile.</p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static1.howtogeekimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/apple-ios-17-5-music-app-recently-played-user-profile.jpg"                      alt="Apple Music on iPhone showcasing the Recently Played section and user profile."                > </p><p> They also shape <a class="link"   href="https://android-pokemon-go.techidaily.com/in-2024-pokemon-go-no-gps-signal-heres-every-possible-solution-on-htc-u23-drfone-by-drfone-virtual-android/" >your Apple Music Replay playlists <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> and radio stations like “For You” and “New Music” which suggests tracks you might like based on past activity. Pausing your listening history in specific situations can ensure your recommendations stay true to your music taste.</p><p> Consider the scenario of parents with young children who hand their iPhones to their children from time to time. You, the parent, want to stop whatever your kids start listening to from influencing your recommendations and appearing on your Apple Music profile. Similarly, when friends borrow your iPhone to play their favorite tracks (like at a party), you probably don’t want those songs to “poison” your recommendations.</p><p> Perhaps you feel like exploring a totally niche music genre you’re generally not a fan of. Or maybe you’re digging a rather obscure album, <a class="link"   href="https://sound-issues.techidaily.com/arctis-9-series-solving-the-dilemma-of-non-functional-mic-units-effectively/" >building collaborative playlists with others <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>, or using SharePlay on CarPlay to let passengers queue up music.</p><p> All of those and similar situations warrant temporarily pausing your listening history. Doing so will also prevent followers from seeing music you’d rather stay hidden from your profile, as long as you remember to enable it before you start listening.</p><h2 id="How-to-Use-Focus-Modes-to-Create-a-Private-Listening-Mode"><a href="#How-to-Use-Focus-Modes-to-Create-a-Private-Listening-Mode" class="headerlink" title="How to Use Focus Modes to Create a Private Listening Mode"></a>How to Use Focus Modes to Create a Private Listening Mode</h2><p> To pause your listening history on Apple Music, you must create a new Focus mode under Settings &gt; Focus on your iPhone or iPad. On a Mac, you’ll find this setting under System Settings &gt; Focus. You’re free to use an existing Focus if you want, but it arguably makes more sense to create a new mode using the “+” plus or “Add Focus” button.</p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static1.howtogeekimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/apple-settings-app-focus-option-selected.png"                      alt="Settings on iPhone with the Focus option selected."                > </p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static1.howtogeekimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/apple-settings-app-focus-add-new-selected.png"                      alt="Focus mode settings on iPhone with the Add New button selected."                > </p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static1.howtogeekimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/apple-settings-app-focus-create-new-options.png"                      alt="Editing Focus options in Settings on iPhone."                > </p><p>Close </p><p> We recommend <a class="link"   href="https://instagram-video-recordings.techidaily.com/updated-storystitcher-compelling-collage-for-instagram-users-for-2024/" >setting up a new Focus mode <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> solely dedicated to controlling your listening history. Give it a recognizable name like “Listening History” and ignore other options like blocking people and apps to ensure you keep receiving essential notifications.</p><p> With a desired Focus mode selected, scroll down to “Focus Filters” and click “Add Filter.” On the next screen, select “Music” from the list of apps and disable the “Use Listening History” switch, then hit “Add” to use this filter with the selected Focus.</p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static1.howtogeekimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/apple-settings-listening-history-focus-add-filter-selected.png"                      alt="Settings on iPhone displaying the Listening History Focus with the Add Filter option selected."                > </p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static1.howtogeekimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/apple-settings-listening-history-focus-filters-apple-music-selected.png"                      alt="Settings on iPhone displaying the Focus Filter options with the Apple Music tile selected.."                > </p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static1.howtogeekimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/apple-settings-listening-history-focus-mode-apple-music-filter-use-listening-history-disabled.png"                      alt="Settings on iPhone showcasing the Apple Music Focus filter with the Use Listening History option disabled."                > </p><p>Close </p><p> You can now temporarily pause your listening history using the “Focus” tile in the Control Center on your iPhone, iPad, or Mac and selecting the focus you just created.</p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static1.howtogeekimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/apple-iphone-control-center-focus-tile-selected.png"                      alt="iPhone&#39;s Control Center with the Focus tile selected."                > </p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static1.howtogeekimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/apple-iphone-control-center-focus-modes.png"                      alt="iPhone&#39;s Control Center with the Listening History tile selected in the Focus Mode section"                > </p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static1.howtogeekimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/apple-iphone-control-center-listening-history-focus-selected.png"                      alt="iPhone&#39;s Control Center with the Listening History Focus mode activated."                > </p><p>Close </p><p> Don’t forget to resume your listening history after you’re done. Simply turn off your “Listening History” Focus in Settings or Control Center and your activity will be saved going forward.</p><p> By default, Focus modes are configured separately on each device. If you’d like to pause your listening history for all devices signed in with the same Apple ID in one fell swoop, be sure to toggle “Share Across Devices” in your “Listening History” Focus settings.</p><h2 id="How-to-Automate-Your-New-Limited-History-Focus-Mode"><a href="#How-to-Automate-Your-New-Limited-History-Focus-Mode" class="headerlink" title="How to Automate Your New Limited History Focus Mode"></a>How to Automate Your New Limited History Focus Mode</h2><p> You can also schedule your Focus by <a class="link"   href="https://extra-lessons.techidaily.com/peak-performance-win-tunes/" >automating it with triggers like location and time <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>. I only listen to energetic beats when I’m in the gym, but that doesn’t mean I’m eager for workout-related music to start popping up in my recommendations.</p><p> To set up a location trigger, open Settings &gt; Focus and select your “Listening History” Focus mode, then hit “Add Schedule” and choose “Location” from the menu. Next, use search to select a desired location like your favorite gym, then hit “Done” to save the changes.</p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static1.howtogeekimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/apple-settings-listening-history-focus-add-schedule-selected.png"                      alt="iPhone&#39;s Settings app with the Add Schedule option selected in the Set a Schedule section."                > </p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static1.howtogeekimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/apple-settings-listening-history-focus-add-schedule-location-selected.png"                      alt="iPhone&#39;s Settings app with the location scheduling option selected for the Listening History Focus mode."                > </p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static1.howtogeekimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/apple-settings-listening-history-focus-add-schedule-location-gym-selected.png"                      alt="iPhone&#39;s Settings app showcasing creating a location schedule for the Listening History Focus mode."                > </p><p>Close </p><p> Maybe your preschooler won’t fall asleep before you play them their favorite . In that case, <a class="link"   href="https://fox-cloud.techidaily.com/updated-in-2024-exclusive-offer-20-free-luts-just-for-dji-mini-and-air-users/" >schedule your Focus <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> for a specific time to stop children from ruining your Apple Music recommendations when it’s nap time. To do so, hit “Add Schedule,” choose “Time,” and define your schedule, such as every night at 10 pm. Hit “Done” when finished.</p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static1.howtogeekimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/apple-settings-listening-history-focus-add-schedule-selected.png"                      alt="iPhone&#39;s Settings app with the Add Schedule option selected in the Set a Schedule section."                > </p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static1.howtogeekimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/apple-settings-listening-history-focus-add-schedule-time-selected.png"                      alt="iPhone&#39;s Settings app with the time scheduling option selected for the Listening History Focus mode."                > </p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static1.howtogeekimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/apple-settings-listening-history-focus-add-schedule-define-timeframe.png"                      alt="iPhone&#39;s Settings app showcasing creating a time schedule for the Listening History Focus mode."                > </p><p>Close </p><h2 id="How-to-Link-Your-“Listening-History”-Focus-to-a-Lock-Screen"><a href="#How-to-Link-Your-“Listening-History”-Focus-to-a-Lock-Screen" class="headerlink" title="How to Link Your “Listening History” Focus to a Lock Screen"></a>How to Link Your “Listening History” Focus to a Lock Screen</h2><p> Consider linking your Focus to a specific Lock Screen so you can quickly enable the “Listening History” Focus by switching to the corresponding Lock Screen. Wake your iPhone and touch and hold the Lock Screen to enter editing mode. Now swipe to the Lock Screen you want, hit the little “Focus” button near the bottom, and select “Listening History.”</p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static1.howtogeekimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/apple-iphone-lock-screen-focus-button-selected.png"                      alt="Editing the Lock Screen on an iPhone, with the Focus button at the bottom selected."                > </p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static1.howtogeekimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/apple-iphone-lock-screen-link-listening-history-focus-mode.png"                      alt="Linking the Listening History focus to a Lock Screen on iPhone."                > </p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static1.howtogeekimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/apple-iphone-lock-screen-listening-history-focus-mode-selected.png"                      alt="iPhone Lock Screen with a linked Focus mode at the bottom highlighted."                > </p><p>Close </p><p> To use your “Listening History” Focus, simply switch to the corresponding Lock Screen.</p><p> On the HomePod and HomePod mini speakers, listening history applies to the Music and Podcasts apps. You can turn the “Update Listening History” on or off for every HomePod and user separately.</p><p> Hit “…” in the Home app and choose “Home Settings” from the menu, then select a user and toggle “Update Listening History” on or off.</p><p> And that’s all there’s to it, really! In just a few minutes, you can create a private listening experience for those times when you don’t want your Apple Music activity to negatively influence your taste profile and the recommendations you get.</p><h2 id="Privacy-Leaks-on-Your-Apple-Music-Profile"><a href="#Privacy-Leaks-on-Your-Apple-Music-Profile" class="headerlink" title="Privacy Leaks on Your Apple Music Profile"></a>Privacy Leaks on Your Apple Music Profile</h2><p> This isn’t the only privacy issue with the Apple Music platform. For example, your profile leaks your listening activity to followers by default. To fix this, you can go with the nuclear option and delete your Apple Music profile or change your settings to make the Music app work precisely how you want.</p><p> You can access these settings using the Music app. First, tap on the “Listen Now” tab and then select your user profile using your profile image followed by “View Profile.” Next, tap “Edit” and change who can follow you, which playlists are featured on your profile, and whether or not “Listening To” is enabled. On a Mac, you’ll need to use the “Additional Privacy Settings” menu to find that last one.</p><p> Looking for more Apple Music tips? Check out all the <a class="link"   href="https://instagram-videos.techidaily.com/new-instagram-storytelling-with-epic-videos/" >best Apple Music features you should already be using <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>.</p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-format="autorelaxed"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="1223367746"></ins></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="8358498916"     data-ad-format="auto"     data-full-width-responsive="true"></ins></p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;The-Smart-Move-Protecting-Yourself-by-Suspending-Listening-Records-on-Apple-Music-Platforms&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#The-Smart-Move-Protecting-You</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="tech" scheme="https://media-tips.techidaily.com/categories/tech/"/>
    
    
    <category term="streaming" scheme="https://media-tips.techidaily.com/tags/streaming/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Exploring the World of Online Entertainment: What to Stream on Your Nintendo Switch?</title>
    <link href="https://media-tips.techidaily.com/exploring-the-world-of-online-entertainment-what-to-stream-on-your-nintendo-switch/"/>
    <id>https://media-tips.techidaily.com/exploring-the-world-of-online-entertainment-what-to-stream-on-your-nintendo-switch/</id>
    <published>2024-08-28T13:59:32.000Z</published>
    <updated>2024-08-29T02:45:25.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="Exploring-the-World-of-Online-Entertainment-What-to-Stream-on-Your-Nintendo-Switch"><a href="#Exploring-the-World-of-Online-Entertainment-What-to-Stream-on-Your-Nintendo-Switch" class="headerlink" title="Exploring the World of Online Entertainment: What to Stream on Your Nintendo Switch?"></a>Exploring the World of Online Entertainment: What to Stream on Your Nintendo Switch?</h2><h3 id="Key-Takeaways"><a href="#Key-Takeaways" class="headerlink" title="Key Takeaways"></a>Key Takeaways</h3><ul><li>YouTube, Hulu, Crunchyroll, and Pokémon TV offer great entertainment options on Nintendo Switch.</li><li>While Twitch was removed after originally being available, Netflix, Prime Video, and Disney+ ahave never been available on the Switch.</li></ul><p> With many titles and franchises to choose from, the Nintendo Switch is a great gaming machine. However, we all need a little break from gaming now and then. Luckily, the Switch has streaming apps that offer great passive entertainment.</p><h2 id="YouTube"><a href="#YouTube" class="headerlink" title="YouTube"></a>YouTube</h2><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static1.howtogeekimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/02/youtube-nintendo-switch.jpg"                      alt="The YouTube app on Nintendo Switch."                > </p><p> YouTube has billions of videos ready to be consumed. No matter your interest, whether it’s how-tos, gaming, comedy, beauty, fashion, technology, and fitness, there’s a content creator for you.</p><p> Most of YouTube’s library is free, but you may run into ads on some of the videos. You can <a class="link"   href="https://extra-approaches.techidaily.com/in-2024-pinnacle-all-in-one-4k-with-touch-display/" >subscribe to YouTube Premium <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>, which gives you an ad-free experience, starting from $13.99 per month. Furthermore, it allows you to unlock more content, such as YouTube original series and movies.</p><h2 id="Hulu"><a href="#Hulu" class="headerlink" title="Hulu"></a>Hulu</h2><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static1.howtogeekimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/02/hulu-switch-1.png"                      alt="Hulu app on Nintendo Switch."                > </p><p> If you’re a fan of movies and series, the Hulu app on Nintendo Switch is for you. The streaming service is known for its great Hulu Originals, including The Bear, Only Murders in the Building, The Handmaid’s Tale, and PEN15.</p><p> Furthermore, through partnerships with Disney (which owns it), Fox, Showtime, and other partners, there’s an expansive library of great entertainment to enjoy. It has also partnered with BBC America, ABC, and ESPN+ to provide live news, sports, and entertainment.</p><p> While the Hulu app is free to download on your Switch, you need a paid subscription to access its content. The basic plan with ads will set you back $7.99 per month. If you want to remove ads or add live TV channels, you’ll have to pay more.</p><p> If you are a new subscriber or an eligible returning customer, Hulu may offer you a one-month free trial to watch its movies and series.</p><h2 id="Crunchyroll"><a href="#Crunchyroll" class="headerlink" title="Crunchyroll"></a>Crunchyroll</h2><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static1.howtogeekimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/02/crunchyroll-nintendo-switch.jpg"                      alt="The Crunchyroll app on Nintendo Switch."                > </p><p> You can catch up on your favorite anime with the Crunchyroll app on Nintendo Switch. <a class="link"   href="https://fix-guide.techidaily.com/how-to-resolve-samsung-galaxy-s23-fe-screen-not-working-drfone-by-drfone-fix-android-problems-fix-android-problems/" >Crunchyroll has a ton of anime <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>, including modern titles like Attack on Titan, Demon Slayer, and Jujutsu Kaisen. You can also find classic anime here, such as Dragon Ball Z, One Piece, and Cowboy Bebop.</p><p> What makes Crunchyroll great is its simulcasts. This means you can watch the latest ongoing anime as it airs in Japan—no need to wait. You can watch anime for free with some limitations (ads and premium locked episodes), on other platforms (PC, Android, and iOS). But, unfortunately, the Nintendo Switch app only works with the premium plans.</p><p> Luckily, there’s a two-week free trial period that works with the Switch app if you’re a new subscriber. Afterward, you can subscribe to the premium plan, starting at $7.99 per month.</p><h2 id="Pokemon-TV"><a href="#Pokemon-TV" class="headerlink" title="Pokémon TV"></a>Pokémon TV</h2><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static1.howtogeekimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/02/pokemon-tv-nintendo-swith.jpg"                      alt="The Pokemon TV app on Nintendo Switch."                > </p><p> With the Pokémon TV app, fans of the popular Nintendo franchise can watch curated Pokémon content for free. This includes specials, movies, episodes, and even entire seasons of the Pokémon anime. It’s a chance to relive or discover some of Ash’s greatest adventures and classic battles.</p><p> Furthermore, the app includes Pokémon Trading Card Game (TCG) tips and strategies. You can also watch Pokémon TCG tournaments worldwide right on your Switch.</p><h2 id="What-Happened-to-the-Twitch-App-on-Nintendo-Switch"><a href="#What-Happened-to-the-Twitch-App-on-Nintendo-Switch" class="headerlink" title="What Happened to the Twitch App on Nintendo Switch?"></a>What Happened to the Twitch App on Nintendo Switch?</h2><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static1.howtogeekimages.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2024/02/twitch-nintendo-switch-statement.jpg"                      alt="The notice that Twitch is discontinuing the Nintendo Switch app."                > </p><p> The Twitch app was removed from the Nintendo eShop on November 6th, 2023. Furthermore, as of January 31st, 2024, people who already own the app on Switch won’t be able to use it. Twitch has completely discontinued the app on the platform.</p><h2 id="Can-You-Get-Netflix-Prime-Video-and-Disney-on-Nintendo-Switch"><a href="#Can-You-Get-Netflix-Prime-Video-and-Disney-on-Nintendo-Switch" class="headerlink" title="Can You Get Netflix, Prime Video, and Disney+ on Nintendo Switch?"></a>Can You Get Netflix, Prime Video, and Disney+ on Nintendo Switch?</h2><p> Unfortunately, Netflix, Prime Video, and Disney have yet to release any apps for Nintendo Switch at the time of writing. That means you’re stuck with YouTube, Hulu, Crunchyroll, and Pokémon TV.</p><hr><p> Don’t be disappointed by the limited selection of streaming apps on the Nintendo Switch. Whether you have the <a class="link"   href="https://win11.techidaily.com/1719355296197-dimming-windows-11-brightness-simple-fixes-unveiled/" >original Switch, OLED, or Lite <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>, remember it’s primarily a gaming console. You shouldn’t expect it to have a wide range of streaming apps like TVs and Smartphones.</p><p> And if you’re looking at these streaming apps because you don’t play games but happen to have a Switch, there are some <a class="link"   href="https://extra-resources.techidaily.com/in-2024-comparison-of-googles-ar-embellishments-to-competitors/" >beginner-friendly games you can try <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>.</p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-format="autorelaxed"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="1223367746"></ins></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="8358498916"     data-ad-format="auto"     data-full-width-responsive="true"></ins></p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;Exploring-the-World-of-Online-Entertainment-What-to-Stream-on-Your-Nintendo-Switch&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#Exploring-the-World-of-Online-Entertai</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="tech" scheme="https://media-tips.techidaily.com/categories/tech/"/>
    
    
    <category term="streaming" scheme="https://media-tips.techidaily.com/tags/streaming/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
</feed>
